<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:20:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"Multiple OS command injection in API and CLI"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-513</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 6.7 An Improper Neutralization of Special Elements used in an OS Command ('OS Command Injection') vulnerability [CWE-78] in FortiWeb may allow an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code on the underlying system via crafted HTTP requests or CLI commands.Fortinet has observed this to be exploited in the wild.FortiAppSec Cloud is NOT impacted by this vulnerability. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Trusted hosts bypass via SSH"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-545</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 1.8 An Improper Privilege Management vulnerability [CWE-269] in FortiOS, FortiProxy and FortiPAM may allow an authenticated administrator to bypass the trusted host policy via crafted CLI command. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SQL injections in voice and administrative interface"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-666</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 7.7 An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in FortiVoice may allow an authenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04969 rev.1 - HPE Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform Servers using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01249, 2025.2 IPU, Intel Processor Stream Cache Advisory, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04969en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04969 rev.1 - HPE Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform Servers using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01249, 2025.2 IPU, Intel Processor Stream Cache Advisory, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicOS SSLVPN Pre-Auth Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0016</link><description>""A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN service allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS), which could cause an impacted firewall to crash. SonicWall PSIRT is not aware of active exploitation in the wild. No reports of a PoC have been made public and malicious use of this vulnerability has not been reported to SonicWall. And SonicWall strongly urges organizations using impacted SonicWall firewalls listed below to follow the provided guidance. NOTE: This vulnerability ONLY impacts the SonicOS SSLVPN interface or service if enabled on the firewall. CVE: CVE-2025-40601 Last updated: Nov. 21, 2025, 12:23 p.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40601
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#november-18-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 142.0.3595.90) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. This update contains a fix for CVE-2025-13223 which has been reported by the Chromium team as having an exploit in the wild. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2025-13223
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"XSS in default error page"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-736</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 4.2 An Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in a Web Page (Basic XSS) vulnerability [CWE-80] in FortiADC virtual server's default error page may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute malicious code via crafted URL. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-40545"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-40545</link><description>""SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted is susceptible to an open redirection vulnerability. The URL is not properly sanitized, and an attacker could manipulate the string to redirect a user to a malicious site. The attack complexity is high, and authentication is required.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40545
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"A Note About Kea Release Notes"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/a-note-about-kea-release-notes</link><description>""Previously, we provided full text copies of the release notes for each version of Kea here in our KB. However, since they are always available directly from our downloads site at https://downloads.isc.org/isc/kea/ and Read the Docs, we felt it would be easier to direct users there for the documentation. If you are looking for Kea release notes, please visit: https://downloads.isc.org/isc/kea/: select the directory of the Kea version you are running. There, you will find zipped downloadable soft ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Buffer Overflow via fortips driver"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-125</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 7.1 A Heap-based Buffer Overflow vulnerability [CWE-122] in FortiClient Windows may allow an authenticated local IPSec user to execute arbitrary code or commands via "fortips_74.sys" driver. The attacker would need to bypass the Windows heap integrity protections. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-40547"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-40547</link><description>""A logic error vulnerability exists in Serv-U which when abused could give a malicious actor with access to admin privileges the ability to execute code. This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40547
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Path confusion vulnerability in GUI"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-910</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 9.4 A relative path traversal vulnerability [CWE-23] in FortiWeb may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute administrative commands on the system via crafted HTTP or HTTPS requests.Fortinet has observed this to be exploited in the wildFortiAppSec Cloud is NOT impacted by this vulnerability. Revised on 2025-11-14 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04973 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04973en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04973 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Cisco Identity Services Engine Reflected Cross-Site Scripting and Information Disclosure Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-ise-multiple-vulns-O9BESWJH</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-20303, CVE-2025-20304, CVE-2025-20305, CVE-2025-20289
**CVSS Score:** 5.4</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Cleartext credentials in diagnose output"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-789</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 3.8 A Cleartext Storage of Sensitive Information in Memory vulnerability [CWE-316] in FortiPAM may allow an authenticated attacker with read-write admin privileges to the CLI to obtain other administrators' credentials via diagnose commands. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stack buffer overflow in CAPWAP daemon"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-632</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 6.9 A stack-based overflow vulnerability [CWE-124] in FortiOS CAPWAP daemon may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker on an adjacent network to achieve arbitrary code execution via sending specially crafted packets. Note that in the default configuration, the attacker must be in control of an authorized FortiAP for the attack to succeed and have access to the same local IP subnet. Additionally, successful exploitation would require defeating stack protection and ASLR. Revised on 2025-11-21 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04888 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking AOS-CX Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04888en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04888 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking AOS-CX Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stack buffer overflow in CAPWAP daemon"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-358</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 6.9 A stack-based overflow vulnerability [CWE-124] in FortiOS and FortiSwitchManager CAPWAP daemon may allow a remote authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code or command as a low privileged user via specially crafted packets.Successful exploitation would require a large amount of effort in preparation because of stack protection and ASLR. Additionally, attacker must be able to pose as an authorized FortiAP or FortiExtender. Revised on 2025-11-21 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CRLF Header Injection in webmail user GUI"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-634</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 3.9 A CRLF Header Injection vulnerability [CWE-93] in FortiMail user GUI may allow an attacker to inject headers in the response via convincing a user to click on a specifically crafted link Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-13223 Type Confusion in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-13223</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2021) for more information. Google is aware that an exploit for CVE-2025-13223 exists in the wild.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-13223
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"File scan result bypass"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-24-501</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 5.0 An Improper Isolation or Compartmentalization vulnerability [CWE-653] in FortiSandbox may allow an unauthenticated attacker to evade the sandboxing scan via a crafted file. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"[製品]Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 公開のお知らせ:2025/11/27 11:00:00"</title><link>https://appweb.trendmicro.com/SupportNews/NewsDetail.aspx?id=5662</link><description>""[公開日時：2025年11月27日(木) 11:00 ] Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 を下記日程にて公開いたします。 ■公開開始日 2025年11月27日(木) ■修正内容・新機能 修正内容・新機能につきましては 最新版ダウンロードページ に掲載のドキュメントをご確認ください。 ■入手方法 本モジュールは弊社Active Updateサーバから配信されます。 ■導入方法 以下製品Q&amp;Aにて適用方法を公開しておりますので、ぜひご確認ください。 製品Q&amp;A: Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 の概要および適用方法 ■製品サポート情報 ご不明な点がございましたら、弊社サポートセンターまでお問合せください。 お問合せ方法については、 こちら をご確認ください。 今後とも弊社製品をご愛顧くださいますよう、よろしくお願い申し上げます。""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00913</link><description>""The BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix (previously know as the "BIND 9 Security Vulnerability Matrix") is a tool to help DNS operators understand the current security risk for a given version of BIND. It has two parts: The first part is a table listing all of the vulnerabilities covered by this page. The first column is a reference number for use in the tables in the second part. The second column is the CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure) number for the vulnerability, linked to its pag ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-0760
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-26391"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-26391</link><description>""SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted XSS Vulnerability. The SolarWinds Platform was susceptible to a XSS vulnerability that affects user-created URL fields. This vulnerability requires authentication from a low-level account.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-26391
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-40549"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-40549</link><description>""A Path Restriction Bypass vulnerability exists in Serv-U that when abused, could give a malicious actor with access to admin privileges the ability to execute code on a directory. This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse. On Windows systems, this scored as medium due to differences in how paths and home directories are handled.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40549
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-40548"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-40548</link><description>""A missing validation process exists in Serv U when abused, could give a malicious actor with access to admin privileges the ability to execute code. This issue requires administrative privileges to abuse.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40548
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Arbitrary memory write via FortIPS driver"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-112</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 7.1 An Exposed IOCTL with Insufficient Access Control vulnerability [CWE-782] in FortiClient Windows may allow an authenticated local user to execute unauthorized code via fortips driver. Success of the attack would require bypassing the Windows memory protections such as Heap integrity and HSP. In addition, it requires a valid and running VPN IPSec connection. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ShareFile users in certain countries may experience issues generating TFA codes during login."</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/t0dh6t0t3dsf</link><description>""Nov 20 , 05:57 EST Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Nov 20 , 05:57 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Nov 20 , 05:54 EST Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Nov 20 , 02:46 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with login"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/jdh5rjrqgwx6</link><description>""Nov 19 , 10:04 EST Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Nov 19 , 10:03 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Nov 19 , 09:48 EST Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Nov 19 , 09:47 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Nov 19 , 09:46 EST Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Nov 19 , 09:30 EST Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented. Nov 19 , 09:13 EST Update - We’re currently experiencing an issue where some users may see an error stating “Unable to get login information.” Our team is working to resolve this as quickly as possible. Please try again after some time. Thank you for your patience! Nov 19 , 08:26 EST Investigating - Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with login into ShareFile. We are investigating this issue and we will provide updates here as soon as available.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Invocation of Process Using Visible Sensitive Information in FortiADC"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-686</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 3.9 An Exposure of Sensitive Information to an Unauthorized Actor vulnerability [CWE-200] in FortiADC Logs may allow an admin with read-only permission to get the external resources password via the logs of the product. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND statement fetches-per-zone"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/bind-statement-fetches-per-zone</link><description>""Name fetches-per-zone Syntax fetches-per-zone [ ( drop | fail ) ]; Blocks options { fetches-per-zone ; ... }; ... view "" { fetches-per-zone ; ... }; Default value(s) If the statement is not used its default value is 0, meaning that the feature is disabled and no queries are dropped. If the statement is used but neither drop nor fail are specified, drop is assumed. Introduced Date: 2015-08-06 Version: 9.10.3b1 Deprecated Still current as of 2025-03-19. De ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/11/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_17.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-13223, CVE-2025-13224
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"EmEditor v25.4.3 を公開しました"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/emeditor-core/emeditor-v25-4-3-%e3%82%92%e5%85%ac%e9%96%8b%e3%81%97%e3%81%be%e3%81%97%e3%81%9f/</link><description>""本日、EmEditor v25.4.3 を公開しました。v25.4.3 には、以下の不具合修正が含まれています。安定した動作のため、常に最新版に更新してご利用ください。 デスクトップ インストーラー版をご使用の場合は、[ […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04970 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking 100 Series Cellular Bridge, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04970en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04970 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking 100 Series Cellular Bridge, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-13224 Type Confusion in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-13224</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2021) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-13224
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Credential leakage through debug commands"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-259</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 5.2 An insufficiently protected credentials vulnerability [CWE-522] in FortiExtender may allow an authenticated user to obtain administrator credentials via debug log commands. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ASP.NET Coreの脆弱性（CVE-2025-55315）に関する注意喚起"</title><link>https://www.skygroup.jp/security-info/news/251114.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-55315
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Authenticated CLI Commands Buffer Overflow"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-251</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 6.3 A buffer overflow vulnerability [CWE-120] in FortiExtender json_cli may allow an authenticated user to execute arbitrary code or commands via crafted CLI commands. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Use of hardcoded password for the redis service"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-843</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 4.8 A use of hard-coded credentials vulnerability [CWE-798] in the internal redis services in FortiWeb may allow an authenticated attacker with shell access to the device to connect to any running redis service and access its data Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"DNSSEC signed zones - best practice guidance relating to NSEC3 signing and validation"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/dnssec-signed-zones-best-practice-guidance-for-nsec3-iterations</link><description>""Overview DNSSEC-signed zones offer protection against response spoofing to both DNSSEC-validating resolvers and authoritative DNS zone operators who choose to sign their published zones. NSEC and NSEC3 are the mechanisms within DNSSEC used to provide proof of non-existence of names. This is achieved by a DNSSEC-signed assurance that between two signed names, no other names exist. NSEC3 uses hash mechanisms to avoid disclosure of the bounding names themselves, otherwise it is possible to establis ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Information disclosure through debug features"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-844</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 4.9 An active debug code vulnerability [CWE-489] in FortiClientWindows may allow a local attacker to run the application step by step and retrieve the saved VPN user password Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Cisco Contact Center Products Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-cc-mult-vuln-gK4TFXSn</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-20377, CVE-2025-20374, CVE-2025-20375, CVE-2025-20376
**CVSS Score:** 6.5</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-54099 Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-54099</link><description>""Acknowledgement added. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-54099
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04971 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking Management Software (AirWave), Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04971en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04971 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking Management Software (AirWave), Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Security Bulletin - November 18 2025"</title><link>https://confluence.atlassian.com/security/security-bulletin-november-18-2025-1671463469.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2023-42282, CVE-2025-489767, CVE-2016-1000027, CVE-2022-311297, CVE-2025-22235, CVE-2024-378907, CVE-2022-31129, CVE-2020-284717, CVE-2024-257108, CVE-2024-21538, CVE-2020-28471, CVE-2022-24785, CVE-2025-41248, CVE-2023-22523, CVE-2024-38999, CVE-2025-222287, CVE-2024-45590, CVE-2025-487348, CVE-2022-41903, CVE-2021-335877, CVE-2023-45133, CVE-2021-33587, CVE-2025-551638, CVE-2023-22522, CVE-2021-233377, CVE-2024-215387, CVE-2025-22228, CVE-2022-46175, CVE-2024-4068, CVE-2022-247727, CVE-2022-1471, CVE-2022-24772, CVE-2021-38037, CVE-2023-524287, CVE-2024-45296, CVE-2022-461757, CVE-2023-46604, CVE-2024-3899910, CVE-2024-455907, CVE-2024-38819, CVE-2024-294158, CVE-2023-22518, CVE-2023-261597, CVE-2020-82037, CVE-2024-29415, CVE-2023-26159, CVE-2024-37890, CVE-2025-222357, CVE-2024-452967, CVE-2022-247717, CVE-2024-40687, CVE-2022-389007, CVE-2025-22166, CVE-2021-3803, CVE-2021-38077, CVE-2023-451339, CVE-2022-23521, CVE-2022-247857, CVE-2023-22527, CVE-2025-221668, CVE-2024-388197, CVE-2023-52428, CVE-2021-3807, CVE-2024-25710, CVE-2023-422829, CVE-2020-8203, CVE-2025-48734, CVE-2025-412487, CVE-2024-22259, CVE-2019-13990, CVE-2023-22524, CVE-2024-222598, CVE-2022-24771, CVE-2025-483878, CVE-2021-23337, CVE-2025-55163
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"EmEditor v25.4.2 を公開しました"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/emeditor-core/emeditor-v25-4-2-%e3%82%92%e5%85%ac%e9%96%8b%e3%81%97%e3%81%be%e3%81%97%e3%81%9f/</link><description>""本日、EmEditor v25.4.2 を公開しました。 v25.4.2 には、以下の不具合修正が含まれています。安定した動作のため、常に最新版に更新してご利用ください。 デスクトップ インストーラー版をご使用の場合は、 […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04963 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors. AMD-SB-3029: Stale Translation Lookaside Buffer (TLB) Entry Vulnerability, Local Unauthorized Access Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04963en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04963 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors. AMD-SB-3029: Stale Translation Lookaside Buffer (TLB) Entry Vulnerability, Local Unauthorized Access Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Out-of-bounds write in multiple endpoints"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/FG-IR-25-225</link><description>""CVSSv3 Score: 6.3 An Out-of-bounds Write vulnerability [CWE-787] in FortiADC may allow an authenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code via specially crafted HTTP requests. Revised on 2025-11-18 00:00:00""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicWall Email Security Affected By Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0018</link><description>""1) CVE-2025-40604 - Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability in the SonicWall Email Security appliance loads root filesystem images without verifying signatures, allowing attackers with VMDK or datastore access to modify system files and gain persistent arbitrary code execution. CVSS Score: 7.2 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H CWE-494: Download of Code Without Integrity Check 2) CVE-2025-40605 - Path Traversal Vulnerability A Path Traversal vulnerability has been identified in the Email Security appliance allows an attacker to manipulate file system paths by injecting crafted directory-traversal sequences (such as ../) and may access files and directories outside the intended restricted path. CVSS Score: 4.9 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N CWE-23: Relative Path Traversal SonicWall strongly advises users of the Email Security products (ES Appliance 5000, 5050, 7000, 7050, 9000, VMWare and Hyper-V) to upgrade to the mentioned fixed release version to address these vulnerabilities. There is currently no evidence any of the vulnerabilities addressed in this release are being exploited in the wild. CVE: CVE-2025-40604, CVE-2025-40605 Last updated: Nov. 19, 2025, 11:42 a.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40604, CVE-2025-40605
**CVSS Score:** 3</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>