<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:31:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"CVE-2025-53773 GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-53773</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-53773
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"EmEditor v25.3.1 を公開しました"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/emeditor-core/emeditor-v25-3-1-%e3%82%92%e5%85%ac%e9%96%8b%e3%81%97%e3%81%be%e3%81%97%e3%81%9f/</link><description>""本日、EmEditor v25.3.1 を公開しました。 v25.3.1 は、次の不具合修正を含みます。安定した動作のため、常に最新版に更新してお使いください。 デスクトップ インストーラー版をご使用の場合は、[ヘルプ] […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace for Windows on ARM - Missing Authorization"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25032/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-49459
**CVSS Score:** 7.8</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBST04945 rev.1 - HPE M-Series Switches Using NVIDIA Cumulus Software, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbst04945en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBST04945 rev.1 - HPE M-Series Switches Using NVIDIA Cumulus Software, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace Clients for Windows - Incorrect Authorization"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25035/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-58134
**CVSS Score:** 4.3</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace VDI Plugin macOS Universal installer for VMware Horizon - Race Condition"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25037/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-58131
**CVSS Score:** 6.6</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace Clients for Windows - Improper Action Enforcement"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25036/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-58135
**CVSS Score:** 5.3</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace Clients - Cross-site Scripting"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25034/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-49461
**CVSS Score:** 4.3</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-9865 Inappropriate implementation in Toolbar"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-9865</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-9865
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Vulnerabilities in Qsync Central"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-22</link><description>""Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported to affect Qsync Central: CVE-2025-29893, CVE-2025-29894: If a remote attacker gains a ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-29894, CVE-2025-29893
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Vulnerabilities in QTS and QuTS hero"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-21</link><description>""Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported to affect certain QNAP operating system versions: CVE-2025-29882: If a remote attacke ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-29882
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Vulnerabilities in Qsync Central"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-28</link><description>""Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported to affect Qsync Central: CVE-2025-30261: Allocation of resources without limits or th ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-30261
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"メディア掲載：レバテックLABにて、EmEditorの歩み・モダン化・これからを語りました"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/reviews/%e3%83%a1%e3%83%87%e3%82%a3%e3%82%a2%e6%8e%b2%e8%bc%89%ef%bc%9a%e3%83%ac%e3%83%90%e3%83%86%e3%83%83%e3%82%aflab%e3%81%ab%e3%81%a6%e3%80%81emeditor%e3%81%ae%e6%ad%a9%e3%81%bf%e3%83%bb%e3%83%a2%e3%83%80/</link><description>""1997年のリリース以来、EmEditorは「超大容量でも軽快」「CSVに強い」を柱に進化してきました。レバテックLABの特集記事では、巨大ファイル処理や検索最適化へのこだわり、CSV編集の実用性、そして近年のCI/CD […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace Clients - Buffer Overflow"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25031/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-49458
**CVSS Score:** 6.5</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-53773 GitHub Copilot and Visual Studio Remote Code Execution Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-53773</link><description>""Updated an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-53773
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-9864 Use after free in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-9864</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-9864
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"K12201527: Overview of Quarterly Security Notifications"</title><link>https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K12201527?utm_source=f5support&amp;utm_medium=RSS</link><description>""Security Advisory Description F5 discloses security vulnerabilities and security exposures for F5 products in Quarterly Security Notifications (QSNs). The dates of future QSNs are published in ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Vulnerabilities in File Station 5"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-19</link><description>""Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported to affect File Station 5: CVE-2025-29874, CVE-2025-29875, CVE-2025-29878, CVE-2025-29 ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-29874, CVE-2025-29878, CVE-2025-29875
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Vulnerability in QuRouter"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-25</link><description>""A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect QuRouter. If a remote attacker gains access to an administrator acco ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-29887
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Vulnerabilities in QVR Firmware for Legacy VioStor NVR"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-29</link><description>""Mutiple vulnerabilities has been reported to affect QVR firmware for legacy VioStor NVR: CVE-2025-52856: A remote attacker can ex ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-52856
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Multiple Vulnerabilities in Netatalk"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-23</link><description>""Multiple vulnerabilities have been reported in Netatalk that affect certain QNAP operating system versions. We have a ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2023-42464, CVE-2022-22995, CVE-2024-38441, CVE-2022-45188, CVE-2024-38439, CVE-2024-38440
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Cisco Webex Meetings URLリダイレクションの脆弱性"</title><link>https://www.cisco.com/c/ja_jp/support/docs/csa/2025/cisco-sa-webex-urlredirect-uK8dDJSZ.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-20291
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04832 rev.1 - HPE Telco Intelligent Assurance, Multiple Netty Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04832en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04832 rev.1 - HPE Telco Intelligent Assurance, Multiple Netty Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Vulnerability in Photo Station"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-24</link><description>""A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect Photo Station. If a remote attacker gains access to a user ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-12923
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#september-5-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 140.0.3485.54) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** "CVE-2025-53791"
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2024-29187 GitHub: CVE-2024-29187 WiX Burn-based bundles are vulnerable to binary hijack when run as SYSTEM"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2024-29187</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-29187
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#august-28-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 139.0.3405.125) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2023-36024, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2022-33639, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2025-21279, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2024-43595, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2024-26246
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-40779: Kea crash upon interaction between specific client options and subnet selection"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/cve-2025-40779</link><description>""CVE: CVE-2025-40779 Title: Kea crash upon interaction between specific client options and subnet selection Document version: 2.0 Posting date: 27 August 2025 Program impacted: Kea Versions affected: Kea 2.7.1 -&gt; 2.7.9 3.0.0 3.1.0 Versions NOT affected: Kea 2.6.0 -&gt; 2.6.4 (Versions prior to 2.6.0 were not assessed.) Versions prior to 2.6.0 are likely unaffected, but were not assessed, as they are end-of-life (EOL). Severity: High Exploitable: Remotely Description: If a DHCPv4 client sends a r ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40779
**CVSS Score:** 7.5</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Zoom Workplace Clients - Argument Injection"</title><link>https://www.zoom.com/en/trust/security-bulletin/ZSB-25033/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-49460
**CVSS Score:** 4.3</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04767 rev.1 - HPE Intelligent Assurance Using Apache, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04767en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04767 rev.1 - HPE Intelligent Assurance Using Apache, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-9867 Inappropriate implementation in Downloads"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-9867</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-9867
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"September 2025"</title><link>https://source.android.com/docs/security/bulletin/2025-09-01</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-32327, CVE-2025-27061, CVE-2025-32347, CVE-2025-20708, CVE-2025-47329, CVE-2025-48545, CVE-2025-48553, CVE-2025-48559, CVE-2025-48544, CVE-2025-46707, CVE-2025-48537, CVE-2025-21755, CVE-2025-32331, CVE-2025-32326, CVE-2025-48526, CVE-2025-48562, CVE-2021-39810, CVE-2025-48539, CVE-2025-48528, CVE-2025-21450, CVE-2025-46710, CVE-2025-47318, CVE-2025-48547, CVE-2025-21432, CVE-2025-32333, CVE-2025-32325, CVE-2025-48524, CVE-2025-47326, CVE-2025-0076, CVE-2025-25180, CVE-2025-32350, CVE-2025-21484, CVE-2025-1706, CVE-2025-21427, CVE-2025-48540, CVE-2025-47328, CVE-2025-27032, CVE-2025-48523, CVE-2025-25179, CVE-2025-48535, CVE-2025-27073, CVE-2025-20696, CVE-2025-48543, CVE-2025-32332, CVE-2025-48560, CVE-2025-26454, CVE-2025-32345, CVE-2025-48552, CVE-2025-38352, CVE-2025-21449, CVE-2025-48538, CVE-2025-48534, CVE-2025-48546, CVE-2025-1246, CVE-2025-21487, CVE-2024-47899, CVE-2025-27043, CVE-2025-27034, CVE-2025-21483, CVE-2025-27042, CVE-2025-32324, CVE-2025-27065, CVE-2023-24023, CVE-2025-48548, CVE-2025-27056, CVE-2025-48561, CVE-2025-46708, CVE-2025-48541, CVE-2025-48527, CVE-2025-0467, CVE-2025-27057, CVE-2025-32349, CVE-2025-32323, CVE-2025-48563, CVE-2025-48558, CVE-2025-48551, CVE-2024-7881, CVE-2025-20703, CVE-2025-21482, CVE-2025-0089, CVE-2025-21464, CVE-2025-27052, CVE-2025-8109, CVE-2025-48531, CVE-2025-48556, CVE-2025-21488, CVE-2025-32346, CVE-2025-21465, CVE-2025-021701, CVE-2025-27066, CVE-2025-21433, CVE-2025-21477, CVE-2025-48550, CVE-2025-32321, CVE-2025-21446, CVE-2025-21454, CVE-2025-26464, CVE-2025-47317, CVE-2025-20704, CVE-2025-48554, CVE-2025-32330, CVE-2025-21481, CVE-2025-48529, CVE-2025-48532, CVE-2025-3212, CVE-2025-48522, CVE-2025-48549, CVE-2025-48542, CVE-2024-47898, CVE-2024-49714
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Vulnerability in License Center"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-27</link><description>""A cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability has been reported to affect License Center. If a remote attacker gains access to an adm ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-22483
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with logging into their ShareFile account"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/6t0mny2zg2nf</link><description>""Aug 28 , 13:54 EDT Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Aug 28 , 13:35 EDT Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues. Aug 28 , 13:25 EDT Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Aug 28 , 13:11 EDT Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented. Aug 28 , 12:52 EDT Investigating - Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with being able to log into their accounts. We are investigating this issue and we will provide updates here as soon as available.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-9478 Use after free in ANGLE"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-9478</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-9478
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Cisco Webex Meetingsのクロスサイトスクリプティングの脆弱性"</title><link>https://www.cisco.com/c/ja_jp/support/docs/csa/2025/cisco-sa-webex-xss-55bv8hhm.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-20328
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Salesloft Drift Application Incident Response"</title><link>https://www.barracuda.com/security/information/salesloft-drift-application-incident-response</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-53791 Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) Security Feature Bypass Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-53791</link><description>""Improper access control in Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) allows an unauthorized attacker to bypass a security feature over a network.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-53791
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-9866 Inappropriate implementation in Extensions"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-9866</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-9866
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Vulnerability in HybridDesk Station"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-20</link><description>""A command injection vulnerability has been reported to affect HybridDesk Station. If an attacker gains local network access, they ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-44015
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"[製品]Trend Micro Mobile Security 9.8 SP5 Critical Patch 7(Build 3404) 公開のお知らせ:2025/09/03 11:00:00"</title><link>https://appweb.trendmicro.com/SupportNews/NewsDetail.aspx?id=5588</link><description>""[公開日時：2025年9月3日 (水) 11:00 ] Trend Micro Mobile Security 9.8 SP5 Critical Patch 7 (Build 3404) を下記日程にて公開いたします。 ■公開開始日 2025年9月3日 (水) ■新機能・修正内容 提供される修正、新機能については付属の Readme ファイルをご確認ください。 ■入手方法 本製品は、 最新版ダウンロードページ よりダウンロードできます。 ■製品サポート情報 ご不明な点がございましたら、弊社サポートセンターまでお問合せください。 お問合せ方法については、 こちら をご確認ください。 今後とも弊社製品をご愛顧くださいますよう、よろしくお願い申し上げます。""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"September Patch Day Notes"</title><link>https://support.sap.com/en/my-support/knowledge-base/security-notes-news/september-2025.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-42926, CVE-2025-42913, CVE-2025-42941, CVE-2025-42961, CVE-2024-13009, CVE-2025-42911, CVE-2023-5072, CVE-2025-42916, CVE-2025-42927, CVE-2025-42925, CVE-2025-42958, CVE-2025-42915, CVE-2025-42918, CVE-2025-27428, CVE-2025-42938, CVE-2025-42930, CVE-2025-22228, CVE-2023-27500, CVE-2025-42922, CVE-2025-42920, CVE-2025-42929, CVE-2025-42923, CVE-2025-42933, CVE-2025-42914, CVE-2025-42944, CVE-2025-42912, CVE-2025-42917
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>