<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:47:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"SonicWall SMA100 10.2.2.2-92sv With Additional File Checking"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0015</link><description>""SonicWall SMA 100 10.2.2.2-92sv build has been released with additional file checking, providing the capability to remove known rootkit malware present on the SMA devices. IMPORTANT: SonicWall strongly recommends that users of the SMA 100 series products (SMA 210, 410, and 500v) upgrade to the 10.2.2.2-92sv version. Additionally, the threat intelligence report from Google Threat Intelligence Group (GTIG) highlights potential risk of using older versions of SMA100 firmware. We strongly recommend that all organizations using SMA 100 Series appliances review and implement the security measures outlined in the KB article linked below. https://www.sonicwall.com/support/notices/urgent-advisory-for-addressing-rootkits-and-other-critical-vulnerabilities-in-sonicwall-sma-100-series-appliances/250730071322160 CVE: N/A Last updated: Sept. 22, 2025, 6:27 p.m.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10890 Side-channel information leakage in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10890</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202 5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10890
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | Salesloft Drift Security Incident"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/salesloft-drift-security-incident</link><description>""09/15/2025 SolarWinds has been made aware of a recent data breach involving Salesforce, which resulted in the unauthorized access and theft of sensitive customer data. learn More &gt; https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/salesloft-drift-security-incident""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10502 Heap buffer overflow in ANGLE"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10502</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10502
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04948 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04948en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04948 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"iOS 18.7 and iPadOS 18.7"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125109</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43358, CVE-2025-43295, CVE-2025-43299, CVE-2025-43359, CVE-2025-43203, CVE-2025-43356, CVE-2025-43346, CVE-2025-43349, CVE-2025-43355, CVE-2025-43362, CVE-2025-43302, CVE-2025-43342
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"iOS 16.7.12 and iPadOS 16.7.12"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125141</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43300
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"macOS Sonoma 14.8"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125112</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43190, CVE-2025-43295, CVE-2025-43312, CVE-2024-27280, CVE-2025-43277, CVE-2025-43293, CVE-2025-43285, CVE-2025-43286, CVE-2025-43310, CVE-2025-43319, CVE-2025-40909, CVE-2025-43231, CVE-2025-31268, CVE-2025-43359, CVE-2025-43304, CVE-2025-31269, CVE-2025-43321, CVE-2025-43349, CVE-2025-43311, CVE-2025-43301, CVE-2025-43302, CVE-2025-43305, CVE-2025-43353, CVE-2025-43332, CVE-2025-43358, CVE-2025-43298, CVE-2025-43355, CVE-2025-43314, CVE-2025-24197, CVE-2025-31255, CVE-2025-31259, CVE-2025-43291, CVE-2025-43326, CVE-2025-43299, CVE-2025-43367, CVE-2025-43273, CVE-2025-43341, CVE-2025-43308, CVE-2025-43315
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10585 Type Confusion in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10585</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information. Google is aware that an exploit for CVE-2025-10585 exists in the wild.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10585
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"macOS Sequoia 15.7"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125111</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43190, CVE-2025-43295, CVE-2025-43312, CVE-2025-43330, CVE-2024-27280, CVE-2025-43293, CVE-2025-43285, CVE-2025-43286, CVE-2025-43310, CVE-2025-43319, CVE-2025-40909, CVE-2025-43304, CVE-2025-31268, CVE-2025-43359, CVE-2025-43321, CVE-2025-43349, CVE-2025-43311, CVE-2025-43301, CVE-2025-43302, CVE-2025-43305, CVE-2025-43353, CVE-2025-43332, CVE-2025-43358, CVE-2025-43298, CVE-2025-43355, CVE-2025-43314, CVE-2025-24197, CVE-2025-31255, CVE-2025-31259, CVE-2025-43291, CVE-2025-43292, CVE-2025-43326, CVE-2025-43299, CVE-2025-43308, CVE-2025-43315
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with uploading files to cloud zones"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/nkh59mkyznrv</link><description>""Sep 23 , 17:26 EDT Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Sep 23 , 17:18 EDT Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Sep 23 , 17:16 EDT Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Sep 23 , 17:08 EDT Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Sep 23 , 16:50 EDT Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented. Sep 23 , 16:42 EDT Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue. Sep 23 , 16:19 EDT Investigating - Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with their accounts. We are investigating this issue and we will provide updates here as soon as available.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10892 Integer overflow in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10892</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202 5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10892
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBGN04919 rev.2 - HPE Intel 700 Series, and I350 Ethernet Controllers, INTEL-SA-01335, Intel Ethernet Drivers for Linux Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbgn04919en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBGN04919 rev.2 - HPE Intel 700 Series, and I350 Ethernet Controllers, INTEL-SA-01335, Intel Ethernet Drivers for Linux Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04857 rev.1 - HPE Superdome Flex and Compute Scale-up Server 3200, Local Buffer Overflow"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04857en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04857 rev.1 - HPE Superdome Flex and Compute Scale-up Server 3200, Local Buffer Overflow""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10501 Use after free in WebRTC"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10501</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10501
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04917 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD, Synergy, Alletra, and Edgeline Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01313, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Xeon Processor Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04917en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04917 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD, Synergy, Alletra, and Edgeline Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01313, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Xeon Processor Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"iOS 15.8.5 and iPadOS 15.8.5"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125142</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43300
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-55232 Microsoft High Performance Compute (HPC) Pack Remote Code Execution Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-55232</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-55232
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04943 rev.2 - HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN Gateways, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04943en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04943 rev.2 - HPE Aruba Networking EdgeConnect SD-WAN Gateways, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Things to be aware of when upgrading to Kea 3.0.0"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/things-to-be-aware-of-when-upgrading-to-kea-300</link><description>""The release of the Kea 3.0 branch brings with it many changes users need to know about. Hooks libraries re-licensed and re-packaged Most Kea hook libraries have become open source and are freely available; the only exceptions are the Role-Based Access Control hook (RBAC) and the Configuration Backend hook (CB), which remain commercially licensed. The open source hook libraries will be available in the Kea source tarball and for package installation from the official ISC repositories on Cloudsmit ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-32801, CVE-2025-32803, CVE-2025-32802
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-76 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Focus for iOS 143.0"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-76/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10290
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"iOS 26 and iPadOS 26"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125108</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43190, CVE-2025-30468, CVE-2025-24133, CVE-2025-43354, CVE-2025-43203, CVE-2025-43303, CVE-2025-43362, CVE-2025-6965, CVE-2025-31254, CVE-2025-43359, CVE-2025-43347, CVE-2025-43349, CVE-2025-43368, CVE-2025-43302, CVE-2025-43342, CVE-2025-43358, CVE-2025-43317, CVE-2025-43344, CVE-2025-43356, CVE-2025-43355, CVE-2025-31255, CVE-2025-43372, CVE-2025-43343, CVE-2025-43357, CVE-2025-43272, CVE-2025-43329, CVE-2025-43346
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-26399"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-26399</link><description>""SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to an unauthenticated AjaxProxy deserialization remote code execution vulnerability that, if exploited, would allow an attacker to run commands on the host machine. This vulnerability is a patch bypass of CVE-2024-28988, which in turn is a patch bypass of CVE-2024-28986.""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-28986, CVE-2025-26399, CVE-2024-28988
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-77 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 143"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-77/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10531, CVE-2025-10537, CVE-2025-10534, CVE-2025-10532, CVE-2025-10533, CVE-2025-10536, CVE-2025-10528, CVE-2025-10530, CVE-2025-10527, CVE-2025-10529
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/09/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_25.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"K12201527: Overview of Quarterly Security Notifications"</title><link>https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K12201527?utm_source=f5support&amp;utm_medium=RSS</link><description>""Security Advisory Description F5 discloses security vulnerabilities and security exposures for F5 products in Quarterly Security Notifications (QSNs). The dates of future QSNs are published in ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10891 Integer overflow in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10891</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202 5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10891
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/09/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_17.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2025-10501, CVE-2025-10500, CVE-2025-10502
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-73 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 143"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-73/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10531, CVE-2025-10537, CVE-2025-10535, CVE-2025-10534, CVE-2025-10532, CVE-2025-10533, CVE-2025-10536, CVE-2025-10528, CVE-2025-10530, CVE-2025-10527, CVE-2025-10529
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04916 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD, Synergy, Alletra, and Edgeline Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01312, Intel TDX Module Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04916en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04916 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD, Synergy, Alletra, and Edgeline Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01312, Intel TDX Module Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#september-25-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 140.0.3485.94) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2025-47967, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2023-36024, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2024-26246, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2024-43595, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2025-21279, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2022-33639
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-10500 Use after free in Dawn"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-10500</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/202[SS9.1]5) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10500
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#september-16-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge for Android Stable Channel (Version 140.0.3485.71). This release includes the most recent security updates from the Chromium project. Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** "CVE-2025-47967"
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/09/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_23.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10892, CVE-2025-10890, CVE-2025-10891
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-78 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 140.3"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-78/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10537, CVE-2025-10532, CVE-2025-10533, CVE-2025-10536, CVE-2025-10528, CVE-2025-10527, CVE-2025-10529
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"EmEditor v25.3.2 を公開しました"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/emeditor-core/emeditor-v25-3-2-%e3%82%92%e5%85%ac%e9%96%8b%e3%81%97%e3%81%be%e3%81%97%e3%81%9f/</link><description>""本日、EmEditor v25.3.2 を公開しました。 v25.3.2 は、次の不具合修正を含みます。安定した動作のため、常に最新版に更新してお使いください。 デスクトップ インストーラー版をご使用の場合は、[ヘルプ] […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04940 rev.1 - HPE Telco Intelligent Assurance, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04940en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04940 rev.1 - HPE Telco Intelligent Assurance, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-75 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox ESR 140.3"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-75/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10537, CVE-2025-10532, CVE-2025-10533, CVE-2025-10536, CVE-2025-10528, CVE-2025-10527, CVE-2025-10529
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Migrating from OpenDNSSEC to BIND 9"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/migrating-from-opendnssec-to-bind-9</link><description>""With OpenDNSSEC reaching End-of-Life, this article aims to help with the transition to BIND 9 for those who wish to do so. In BIND 9 you can configure a DNSSEC Key and Signing Policy (KASP), allowing you to specify all DNSSEC signing behavior in one place. This is the same approach as with OpenDNSSEC. Requirements First of all, OpenSSL 3.0 or higher is required. Older versions relied on so-called engines to perform cryptographic operations. The PKCS#11 engine was used to interface with an HSM ke ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04662 rev.7 - RADIUS protocol susceptible to forgery attacks"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04662en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04662 rev.7 - RADIUS protocol susceptible to forgery attacks""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04950 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM), Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS)"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04950en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04950 rev.1 - HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM), Reflected Cross Site Scripting (XSS)""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Security Bulletin - September 16 2025"</title><link>https://confluence.atlassian.com/security/security-bulletin-september-16-2025-1627098357.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2023-22523, CVE-2023-22522, CVE-2022-23521, CVE-2019-13990, CVE-2023-46604, CVE-2025-48734, CVE-2022-1471, CVE-2022-41903, CVE-2023-22524, CVE-2023-22518, CVE-2025-53506, CVE-2025-52520, CVE-2023-22527
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#september-19-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 140.0.3485.81) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. This update contains a fix for CVE-2025-10585 which has been reported by the Chromium team as having an exploit in the wild. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10585
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-47967 Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) for Android Spoofing Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-47967</link><description>""Insufficient ui warning of dangerous operations in Microsoft Edge for Android allows an unauthorized attacker to perform spoofing over a network.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-47967
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"macOS Tahoe 26"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125110</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43190, CVE-2025-43330, CVE-2025-43304, CVE-2025-31268, CVE-2025-43347, CVE-2025-43368, CVE-2025-43302, CVE-2025-43298, CVE-2025-43314, CVE-2025-31271, CVE-2025-43283, CVE-2025-43291, CVE-2025-43316, CVE-2025-43341, CVE-2025-31270, CVE-2025-43315, CVE-2025-43285, CVE-2025-43294, CVE-2025-43337, CVE-2025-6965, CVE-2025-43293, CVE-2025-43319, CVE-2025-43204, CVE-2025-43311, CVE-2025-43366, CVE-2025-24088, CVE-2025-43207, CVE-2025-43344, CVE-2025-43279, CVE-2025-43357, CVE-2025-43367, CVE-2025-43262, CVE-2025-43333, CVE-2025-43295, CVE-2025-43312, CVE-2025-43354, CVE-2025-43331, CVE-2024-27280, CVE-2025-43287, CVE-2025-43286, CVE-2025-40909, CVE-2025-43325, CVE-2025-43328, CVE-2025-31269, CVE-2025-43321, CVE-2025-43349, CVE-2025-43318, CVE-2025-43301, CVE-2025-43342, CVE-2025-43358, CVE-2025-43356, CVE-2025-43355, CVE-2025-24197, CVE-2025-31255, CVE-2025-31259, CVE-2025-43372, CVE-2025-43327, CVE-2025-43369, CVE-2025-43340, CVE-2025-43303, CVE-2025-43208, CVE-2025-43310, CVE-2025-43297, CVE-2025-43359, CVE-2025-43305, CVE-2025-43353, CVE-2025-43332, CVE-2025-43317, CVE-2025-43307, CVE-2025-43343, CVE-2025-43292, CVE-2025-43326, CVE-2025-43272, CVE-2025-43299, CVE-2025-43329, CVE-2025-43346, CVE-2025-43308
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-74 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox ESR 115.28"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-74/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-10533
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>