<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"K12201527: Overview of Quarterly Security Notifications"</title><link>https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K12201527?utm_source=f5support&amp;utm_medium=RSS</link><description>""Security Advisory Description F5 discloses security vulnerabilities and security exposures for F5 products in Quarterly Security Notifications (QSNs). The dates of future QSNs are published in ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00913</link><description>""The BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix (previously know as the "BIND 9 Security Vulnerability Matrix") is a tool to help DNS operators understand the current security risk for a given version of BIND. It has two parts: The first part is a table listing all of the vulnerabilities covered by this page. The first column is a reference number for use in the tables in the second part. The second column is the CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure) number for the vulnerability, linked to its pag ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-0760
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04944 rev.1 - HPE Superdome Flex 280 and Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04944en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04944 rev.1 - HPE Superdome Flex 280 and Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"DNSSEC signed zones - best practice guidance relating to NSEC3 signing and validation"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/dnssec-signed-zones-best-practice-guidance-for-nsec3-iterations</link><description>""Overview DNSSEC-signed zones offer protection against response spoofing to both DNSSEC-validating resolvers and authoritative DNS zone operators who choose to sign their published zones. NSEC and NSEC3 are the mechanisms within DNSSEC used to provide proof of non-existence of names. This is achieved by a DNSSEC-signed assurance that between two signed names, no other names exist. NSEC3 uses hash mechanisms to avoid disclosure of the bounding names themselves, otherwise it is possible to establis ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"December 2025"</title><link>https://source.android.com/docs/security/bulletin/2025-12-01</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-48599, CVE-2025-25177, CVE-2025-48603, CVE-2025-48565, CVE-2025-48610, CVE-2025-48618, CVE-2025-48572, CVE-2025-27054, CVE-2025-48621, CVE-2025-48614, CVE-2025-22432, CVE-2025-48600, CVE-2025-32328, CVE-2025-48596, CVE-2025-20726, CVE-2025-61609, CVE-2025-61617, CVE-2025-48575, CVE-2025-47370, CVE-2023-40130, CVE-2025-20727, CVE-2025-47382, CVE-2025-22420, CVE-2025-20752, CVE-2025-48629, CVE-2025-48615, CVE-2025-47323, CVE-2025-48580, CVE-2025-48622, CVE-2025-20790, CVE-2025-48638, CVE-2025-48598, CVE-2025-31717, CVE-2025-48620, CVE-2025-48525, CVE-2025-48639, CVE-2025-48555, CVE-2025-47372, CVE-2025-20791, CVE-2025-47319, CVE-2025-48589, CVE-2025-48564, CVE-2025-38236, CVE-2025-61619, CVE-2025-48617, CVE-2025-48591, CVE-2025-20757, CVE-2025-61607, CVE-2025-48584, CVE-2025-48627, CVE-2025-20730, CVE-2025-48624, CVE-2025-20792, CVE-2025-20754, CVE-2025-48623, CVE-2025-48628, CVE-2025-48607, CVE-2025-11133, CVE-2025-48637, CVE-2025-38349, CVE-2025-11131, CVE-2025-48590, CVE-2025-20756, CVE-2025-48573, CVE-2025-48604, CVE-2025-6349, CVE-2025-48576, CVE-2025-61618, CVE-2025-20751, CVE-2025-46711, CVE-2025-8045, CVE-2025-27074, CVE-2025-47354, CVE-2025-27053, CVE-2025-48594, CVE-2025-31718, CVE-2025-20753, CVE-2025-61610, CVE-2025-3012, CVE-2024-35970, CVE-2025-48631, CVE-2025-48588, CVE-2025-38500, CVE-2025-48583, CVE-2025-32329, CVE-2025-20758, CVE-2025-48586, CVE-2025-48592, CVE-2025-48612, CVE-2025-61608, CVE-2025-11132, CVE-2025-48632, CVE-2025-32319, CVE-2025-48597, CVE-2025-27070, CVE-2025-20750, CVE-2025-48601, CVE-2025-58410, CVE-2025-48536, CVE-2025-48566, CVE-2025-6573, CVE-2025-20755, CVE-2025-20759, CVE-2025-20725, CVE-2025-48626, CVE-2025-47351, CVE-2025-48633
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"A Note About Kea Release Notes"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/a-note-about-kea-release-notes</link><description>""Previously, we provided full text copies of the release notes for each version of Kea here in our KB. However, since they are always available directly from our downloads site at https://downloads.isc.org/isc/kea/ and Read the Docs, we felt it would be easier to direct users there for the documentation. If you are looking for Kea release notes, please visit: https://downloads.isc.org/isc/kea/: select the directory of the Kea version you are running. There, you will find zipped downloadable soft ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04973 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04973en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04973 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-54099 Windows Ancillary Function Driver for WinSock Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-54099</link><description>""Acknowledgement added. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-54099
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"[製品]Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 公開のお知らせ:2025/11/27 11:00:00"</title><link>https://appweb.trendmicro.com/SupportNews/NewsDetail.aspx?id=5662</link><description>""[公開日時：2025年11月27日(木) 11:00 ] Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 を下記日程にて公開いたします。 ■公開開始日 2025年11月27日(木) ■修正内容・新機能 修正内容・新機能につきましては 最新版ダウンロードページ に掲載のドキュメントをご確認ください。 ■入手方法 本モジュールは弊社Active Updateサーバから配信されます。 ■導入方法 以下製品Q&amp;Aにて適用方法を公開しておりますので、ぜひご確認ください。 製品Q&amp;A: Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 の概要および適用方法 ■製品サポート情報 ご不明な点がございましたら、弊社サポートセンターまでお問合せください。 お問合せ方法については、 こちら をご確認ください。 今後とも弊社製品をご愛顧くださいますよう、よろしくお願い申し上げます。""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ShareFile users in certain countries may experience issues generating TFA codes during login."</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/t0dh6t0t3dsf</link><description>""Nov 20 , 05:57 EST Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Nov 20 , 05:57 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Nov 20 , 05:54 EST Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Nov 20 , 02:46 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with login"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/jdh5rjrqgwx6</link><description>""Nov 19 , 10:04 EST Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Nov 19 , 10:03 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Nov 19 , 09:48 EST Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Nov 19 , 09:47 EST Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Nov 19 , 09:46 EST Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Nov 19 , 09:30 EST Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented. Nov 19 , 09:13 EST Update - We’re currently experiencing an issue where some users may see an error stating “Unable to get login information.” Our team is working to resolve this as quickly as possible. Please try again after some time. Thank you for your patience! Nov 19 , 08:26 EST Investigating - Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with login into ShareFile. We are investigating this issue and we will provide updates here as soon as available.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicOS SSLVPN Pre-Auth Stack-Based Buffer Overflow Vulnerability"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0016</link><description>""A Stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability in the SonicOS SSLVPN service allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to cause Denial of Service (DoS), which could cause an impacted firewall to crash. SonicWall PSIRT is not aware of active exploitation in the wild. No reports of a PoC have been made public and malicious use of this vulnerability has not been reported to SonicWall. And SonicWall strongly urges organizations using impacted SonicWall firewalls listed below to follow the provided guidance. NOTE: This vulnerability ONLY impacts the SonicOS SSLVPN interface or service if enabled on the firewall. CVE: CVE-2025-40601 Last updated: Nov. 21, 2025, 12:23 p.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40601
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"EmEditor v25.4.3 を公開しました"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/emeditor-core/emeditor-v25-4-3-%e3%82%92%e5%85%ac%e9%96%8b%e3%81%97%e3%81%be%e3%81%97%e3%81%9f/</link><description>""本日、EmEditor v25.4.3 を公開しました。v25.4.3 には、以下の不具合修正が含まれています。安定した動作のため、常に最新版に更新してご利用ください。 デスクトップ インストーラー版をご使用の場合は、[ […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicWall Email Security Affected By Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0018</link><description>""1) CVE-2025-40604 - Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability Download of Code Without Integrity Check Vulnerability in the SonicWall Email Security appliance loads root filesystem images without verifying signatures, allowing attackers with VMDK or datastore access to modify system files and gain persistent arbitrary code execution. CVSS Score: 7.2 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:H/A:H CWE-494: Download of Code Without Integrity Check 2) CVE-2025-40605 - Path Traversal Vulnerability A Path Traversal vulnerability has been identified in the Email Security appliance allows an attacker to manipulate file system paths by injecting crafted directory-traversal sequences (such as ../) and may access files and directories outside the intended restricted path. CVSS Score: 4.9 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.0/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:H/I:N/A:N CWE-23: Relative Path Traversal SonicWall strongly advises users of the Email Security products (ES Appliance 5000, 5050, 7000, 7050, 9000, VMWare and Hyper-V) to upgrade to the mentioned fixed release version to address these vulnerabilities. There is currently no evidence any of the vulnerabilities addressed in this release are being exploited in the wild. CVE: CVE-2025-40604, CVE-2025-40605 Last updated: Nov. 19, 2025, 11:42 a.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40604, CVE-2025-40605
**CVSS Score:** 3</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>