<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:27:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00913</link><description>""The BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix (previously know as the "BIND 9 Security Vulnerability Matrix") is a tool to help DNS operators understand the current security risk for a given version of BIND. It has two parts: The first part is a table listing all of the vulnerabilities covered by this page. The first column is a reference number for use in the tables in the second part. The second column is the CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure) number for the vulnerability, linked to its pag ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-0760
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"DNSSEC signed zones - best practice guidance relating to NSEC3 signing and validation"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/dnssec-signed-zones-best-practice-guidance-for-nsec3-iterations</link><description>""Overview DNSSEC-signed zones offer protection against response spoofing to both DNSSEC-validating resolvers and authoritative DNS zone operators who choose to sign their published zones. NSEC and NSEC3 are the mechanisms within DNSSEC used to provide proof of non-existence of names. This is achieved by a DNSSEC-signed assurance that between two signed names, no other names exist. NSEC3 uses hash mechanisms to avoid disclosure of the bounding names themselves, otherwise it is possible to establis ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04974 rev.1 - HPE Unified OSS Console Assurance Monitoring (UOCAM), Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04974en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04974 rev.1 - HPE Unified OSS Console Assurance Monitoring (UOCAM), Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBCR04980 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01312, Intel TDX Module Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbcr04980en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBCR04980 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01312, Intel TDX Module Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04972 Rev. 1 - HPE Telco Network Function Virtual Orchestrator, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04972en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04972 Rev. 1 - HPE Telco Network Function Virtual Orchestrator, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ESET Customer Advisory: Modules Review, October 2025"</title><link>https://support-feed.eset.com/link/15370/17217198/ca8889</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBCR04981 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01313, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Xeon Processor Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbcr04981en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBCR04981 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01313, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Xeon Processor Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#december-4-2025</link><description>"Microsoft has released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 143.0.3650.66) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** "CVE-2025-62223"
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/12/stable-channel-update-for-desktop.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-13721, CVE-2025-13720, CVE-2025-13631, CVE-2025-13640, CVE-2025-13635, CVE-2025-13633, CVE-2025-13632, CVE-2025-13639, CVE-2025-13630, CVE-2025-13637, CVE-2025-13636, CVE-2025-13634, CVE-2025-13638
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBCR04982 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using UEFI, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbcr04982en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBCR04982 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using UEFI, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Securing the MySQL Connection"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/securing-the-mysql-connection</link><description>""Enabling TLS with MySQL Modern SQL databases, such as MySQL, its variants, and PostgreSQL, can protect communication between clients, such as Kea, and servers using SSL/TLS. In MySQL, the TLS configuration is split between clients and servers, so to enable TLS, you need to update both the Kea and MySQL server configuration. Checking the TLS support status of your MySQL installation Most MySQL installations have TLS enabled during compilation time. However, some deployments may have it disabled. ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04976 rev.1 - HPE Virtualized Telecommunication Management Information Platform (vTeMIP), Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04976en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04976 rev.1 - HPE Virtualized Telecommunication Management Information Platform (vTeMIP), Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04944 rev.1 - HPE Superdome Flex 280 and Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04944en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04944 rev.1 - HPE Superdome Flex 280 and Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"[製品]Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 公開のお知らせ:2025/11/27 11:00:00"</title><link>https://appweb.trendmicro.com/SupportNews/NewsDetail.aspx?id=5662</link><description>""[公開日時：2025年11月27日(木) 11:00 ] Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 を下記日程にて公開いたします。 ■公開開始日 2025年11月27日(木) ■修正内容・新機能 修正内容・新機能につきましては 最新版ダウンロードページ に掲載のドキュメントをご確認ください。 ■入手方法 本モジュールは弊社Active Updateサーバから配信されます。 ■導入方法 以下製品Q&amp;Aにて適用方法を公開しておりますので、ぜひご確認ください。 製品Q&amp;A: Trend Micro Apex One (Mac) Patch 18 の概要および適用方法 ■製品サポート情報 ご不明な点がございましたら、弊社サポートセンターまでお問合せください。 お問合せ方法については、 こちら をご確認ください。 今後とも弊社製品をご愛顧くださいますよう、よろしくお願い申し上げます。""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBUX04977 rev.1 - HP-UX Using OpenSSL, Memory Corruption and Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbux04977en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBUX04977 rev.1 - HP-UX Using OpenSSL, Memory Corruption and Remote Code Execution Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"A Note About Kea Release Notes"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/a-note-about-kea-release-notes</link><description>""Previously, we provided full text copies of the release notes for each version of Kea here in our KB. However, since they are always available directly from our downloads site at https://downloads.isc.org/isc/kea/ and Read the Docs, we felt it would be easier to direct users there for the documentation. If you are looking for Kea release notes, please visit: https://downloads.isc.org/isc/kea/: select the directory of the Kea version you are running. There, you will find zipped downloadable soft ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBCR04979 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbcr04979en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBCR04979 rev.1 - HPE Cray XD670 Server Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"December 2025"</title><link>https://source.android.com/docs/security/bulletin/2025-12-01</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-48525, CVE-2025-48620, CVE-2025-48572, CVE-2025-48565, CVE-2025-48637, CVE-2025-27070, CVE-2025-48601, CVE-2025-48622, CVE-2025-22432, CVE-2025-48618, CVE-2025-20730, CVE-2025-48626, CVE-2025-32329, CVE-2025-47370, CVE-2025-20755, CVE-2025-48573, CVE-2025-48629, CVE-2025-48590, CVE-2025-20756, CVE-2025-61610, CVE-2025-20792, CVE-2025-48594, CVE-2025-61617, CVE-2025-20750, CVE-2025-48614, CVE-2025-20753, CVE-2025-48633, CVE-2025-48576, CVE-2025-48586, CVE-2025-20759, CVE-2025-48610, CVE-2024-35970, CVE-2025-27054, CVE-2025-61607, CVE-2025-61608, CVE-2025-20727, CVE-2025-22420, CVE-2025-46711, CVE-2025-38500, CVE-2025-20726, CVE-2025-48596, CVE-2025-48639, CVE-2025-48575, CVE-2023-40130, CVE-2025-48583, CVE-2025-47319, CVE-2025-47354, CVE-2025-48580, CVE-2025-8045, CVE-2025-20754, CVE-2025-38349, CVE-2025-48600, CVE-2025-20790, CVE-2025-48592, CVE-2025-48631, CVE-2025-48584, CVE-2025-48604, CVE-2025-48597, CVE-2025-48591, CVE-2025-32319, CVE-2025-47382, CVE-2025-20791, CVE-2025-61609, CVE-2025-47351, CVE-2025-48566, CVE-2025-48603, CVE-2025-61619, CVE-2025-58410, CVE-2025-3012, CVE-2025-48607, CVE-2025-6573, CVE-2025-20758, CVE-2025-20752, CVE-2025-48555, CVE-2025-20751, CVE-2025-38236, CVE-2025-48536, CVE-2025-48632, CVE-2025-48615, CVE-2025-48564, CVE-2025-48627, CVE-2025-47372, CVE-2025-48624, CVE-2025-48623, CVE-2025-48588, CVE-2025-48638, CVE-2025-47323, CVE-2025-11132, CVE-2025-27053, CVE-2025-31718, CVE-2025-48598, CVE-2025-48612, CVE-2025-6349, CVE-2025-48621, CVE-2025-61618, CVE-2025-32328, CVE-2025-25177, CVE-2025-20757, CVE-2025-27074, CVE-2025-20725, CVE-2025-48628, CVE-2025-31717, CVE-2025-11131, CVE-2025-48599, CVE-2025-11133, CVE-2025-48589
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>