<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:51:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#december-11-2025</link><description>"Microsoft released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 143.0.3650.80) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. The Chromium team reported that CVEâ2025â14174 has an exploit in the wild, and this update contains a fix for it. For more information, see the Security Update Guide"

**CVE:** CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2024-43595, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2022-33639, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2025-62223, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2025-21279, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2024-26246, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2025-60711, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2025-13223, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2025-47967, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2023-36024
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Remote Code Execution Vulnerability in React and Next.js Frameworks: December 2025"</title><link>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-react-flight-TYw32Ddb</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-55182
**CVSS Score:** 10.0</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"iOS 18.7.3 and iPadOS 18.7.3"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125885</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43539, CVE-2025-14174, CVE-2025-43542, CVE-2025-9086, CVE-2025-46279, CVE-2025-43531, CVE-2024-7264, CVE-2025-43529, CVE-2025-46292, CVE-2025-46287, CVE-2025-43532, CVE-2025-43538, CVE-2025-46276, CVE-2025-5918, CVE-2025-43535, CVE-2025-43541, CVE-2025-43536, CVE-2025-46285, CVE-2025-43512, CVE-2025-43530, CVE-2025-43501
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ESET Customer Advisory: Modules Review, November 2025"</title><link>https://support-feed.eset.com/link/15370/17236113/ca8899</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND block options"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/bind-block-options</link><description>""Name options Syntax options { ... }; Blocks topmost Default value(s) None Introduced Date: 1997-05-06 BIND version: 8.1.1 Deprecated Still current as of 2025-11-24 Description The options block does not have to be present in the BIND configuration file, if there are no options to set, or to change from their default values. Thus there is no default value for options as such, it being a container in which other statements are put, rather than defining anything itself. The syntax shown abov ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-98 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 146.0.1"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-98/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14860, CVE-2025-14861
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/12/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_16.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14766, CVE-2025-14765
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04954 rev.2 - HPE Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform, HPE Superdome Flex and HPE Superdome Flex 280 servers, Security Bypass Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04954en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04954 rev.2 - HPE Compute Scale-up Server 3200 Platform, HPE Superdome Flex and HPE Superdome Flex 280 servers, Security Bypass Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"PHP 8.1.34 Released!"</title><link>https://www.php.net/archive/2025.php#2025-12-18-5</link><description>"The PHP development team announces the immediate availability of PHP 8.1.34. This is a security release. All PHP 8.1 users are encouraged to upgrade to this version. For source downloads of PHP 8.1.34 please visit our downloads page, Windows source and binaries can also be found there. The list of changes is recorded in the ChangeLog."

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"K12201527: Overview of Quarterly Security Notifications"</title><link>https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K12201527?utm_source=f5support&amp;utm_medium=RSS</link><description>""Security Advisory Description F5 discloses security vulnerabilities and security exposures for F5 products in Quarterly Security Notifications (QSNs). The dates of future QSNs are published in ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Planned Billing and Purchasing System Updates"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/2rhh0ns7y25g</link><description>""Dec 20 , 05:30 EST Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed. Dec 20 , 04:00 EST In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary. Dec 18 , 12:07 EST Scheduled - Our billing and purchasing services will be disabled from Saturday, Dec 20th at 4:00 AM EST to Saturday, Dec 20th at 05:30 AM EST. Please check back after Saturday, Dec 20th at 05:30 AM EST to make any billing changes or ShareFile purchases. Thank you for your business.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"PHP 8.5.1 Released!"</title><link>https://www.php.net/archive/2025.php#2025-12-18-1</link><description>"The PHP development team announces the immediate availability of PHP 8.5.1. This is a security release. All PHP 8.5 users are encouraged to upgrade to this version. For source downloads of PHP 8.5.1 please visit our downloads page, Windows source and binaries can also be found there. The list of changes is recorded in the ChangeLog."

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2024-30099 Windows Kernel Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2024-30099</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-30099
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-21367 Windows Win32 Kernel Subsystem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-21367</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-21367
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"macOS Sequoia 15.7.3"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125887</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43539, CVE-2025-43522, CVE-2025-43516, CVE-2025-43542, CVE-2025-43519, CVE-2025-43463, CVE-2025-43509, CVE-2025-43521, CVE-2025-9086, CVE-2025-43513, CVE-2025-43320, CVE-2025-43527, CVE-2025-43482, CVE-2024-7264, CVE-2025-46287, CVE-2025-46289, CVE-2025-43416, CVE-2025-43532, CVE-2025-46276, CVE-2025-5918, CVE-2025-43523, CVE-2025-43517, CVE-2025-46285, CVE-2025-43518, CVE-2025-43512, CVE-2025-43530
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"iOS 26.2 and iPadOS 26.2"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125884</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43539, CVE-2025-14174, CVE-2025-43542, CVE-2025-9086, CVE-2025-43533, CVE-2025-43428, CVE-2025-46279, CVE-2025-43531, CVE-2025-43511, CVE-2024-7264, CVE-2025-46288, CVE-2025-43529, CVE-2025-46292, CVE-2025-46287, CVE-2025-46277, CVE-2025-43532, CVE-2025-43538, CVE-2025-46276, CVE-2025-5918, CVE-2025-43535, CVE-2025-43541, CVE-2025-43536, CVE-2025-46285, CVE-2025-43475, CVE-2025-43518, CVE-2025-43501
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04986 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04986en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04986 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Activator, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Operational Notification: Impact of Stricter Glue Checking"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/strict-glue</link><description>""Title: Operational Notification: Impact of Stricter Glue Checking Document Version: 1.0 Posting date: 15 December 2025 Canonical URL: https://kb.isc.org/docs/strict-glue Program impacted: BIND Versions affected: BIND 9.18.41 and later 9.20.15 and later 9.21.14 and later Description: BIND versions released in October 2025 included changes in how BIND processes referrals in delegations. BIND now only trusts glue records if, in the associated NS record, the target name (right side) is a subdomai ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"PHP 8.2.30 Released!"</title><link>https://www.php.net/archive/2025.php#2025-12-18-3</link><description>"The PHP development team announces the immediate availability of PHP 8.2.30. This is a security release. All PHP 8.2 users are encouraged to upgrade to this version. For source downloads of PHP 8.2.30 please visit our downloads page, Windows source and binaries can also be found there. The list of changes is recorded in the ChangeLog."

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESB3P04984 rev.1 - HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD Alletra and Synergy Servers Using Intel QuickAssist Technology Software Drivers, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesb3p04984en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESB3P04984 rev.1 - HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD Alletra and Synergy Servers Using Intel QuickAssist Technology Software Drivers, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04989 rev.1 - HPE Unified OSS Console Assurance Monitoring (UOCAM), Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04989en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04989 rev.1 - HPE Unified OSS Console Assurance Monitoring (UOCAM), Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-14766 Use after free in WebGPU"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-14766</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14766
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBGN04985 rev.2 - Hewlett Packard Enterprise OneView Software, Remote Code Execution"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbgn04985en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBGN04985 rev.2 - Hewlett Packard Enterprise OneView Software, Remote Code Execution""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"PHP 8.3.29 Released!"</title><link>https://www.php.net/archive/2025.php#2025-12-18-2</link><description>"The PHP development team announces the immediate availability of PHP 8.3.29. This is a security release. All PHP 8.3 users are encouraged to upgrade to this version. For source downloads of PHP 8.3.29 please visit our downloads page, Windows source and binaries can also be found there. The list of changes is recorded in the ChangeLog."

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-24044 Windows Win32 Kernel Subsystem Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-24044</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-24044
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"How to Report or Inquire About Potential Software Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-01020</link><description>""ISC does not pay bug bounties. If you suspect you have found a vulnerability in BIND, ISC DHCP, Kea DHCP, or Stork, or if you wish to inquire about a vulnerability that you have learned about which has not yet been publicly announced, ISC requests you to follow the process described at https://www.isc.org/security-report/. We ask reporters to Notify us as soon as possible after you discover a real or potential security issue. Provide us a reasonable amount of time to resolve the issue before yo ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Reports About Cyberattacks Against Cisco Secure Email Gateway And Cisco Secure Email and Web Manager"</title><link>https://sec.cloudapps.cisco.com/security/center/content/CiscoSecurityAdvisory/cisco-sa-sma-attack-N9bf4</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-20393
**CVSS Score:** 10.0</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"macOS Tahoe 26.2"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125886</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43539, CVE-2025-43522, CVE-2025-46283, CVE-2025-43516, CVE-2025-14174, CVE-2025-43542, CVE-2025-46278, CVE-2025-43519, CVE-2025-46291, CVE-2025-43509, CVE-2025-43521, CVE-2025-9086, CVE-2025-43513, CVE-2025-43533, CVE-2025-43410, CVE-2025-46281, CVE-2025-43428, CVE-2025-43514, CVE-2025-46279, CVE-2025-43527, CVE-2025-43482, CVE-2025-43531, CVE-2025-43511, CVE-2024-7264, CVE-2025-46288, CVE-2025-43529, CVE-2025-46287, CVE-2025-46289, CVE-2024-8906, CVE-2025-46277, CVE-2025-43416, CVE-2025-46282, CVE-2025-43532, CVE-2025-43538, CVE-2025-46276, CVE-2025-5918, CVE-2025-43535, CVE-2025-43541, CVE-2025-43526, CVE-2025-43536, CVE-2025-43523, CVE-2025-43517, CVE-2025-46285, CVE-2025-43518, CVE-2025-43512, CVE-2025-43530, CVE-2025-43501
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-14372 Use after free in Password Manager"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-14372</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2021) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14372
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"RCE Vulnerabilities in Barracuda RMM Service Center – Hotfix Available"</title><link>https://trust.barracuda.com/security/information/rce-vulnerabilities-barracuda-rmm-service-center-hotfix-availabile</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-34392, CVE-2025-34394, CVE-2025-34395, CVE-2025-34393
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicWall SMA1000 appliance local privilege escalation vulnerability"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0019</link><description>""A local privilege escalation vulnerability due to insufficient authorization in the SonicWall SMA1000 appliance management console (AMC). Please note that SonicWall Firewall products are not affected by this vulnerability. CVE: CVE-2025-40602 Last updated: Dec. 18, 2025, 11:34 a.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40602
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE‑2025‑14174 Chromium: CVE-2025-14174 Out of bounds memory access in ANGLE"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE%E2%80%912025%E2%80%9114174</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information. Google is aware that an exploit for CVE-2025-14174 exists in the wild.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14174
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ShareFile Planned Maintenance"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/xd7tm0xzd473</link><description>""Dec 13 , 00:50 EST Completed - The scheduled maintenance has been completed. Dec 13 , 00:42 EST Verifying - Verification is currently underway for maintenance items. Dec 12 , 21:30 EST In progress - Scheduled maintenance is currently in progress. We will provide updates as necessary. Dec 11 , 03:32 EST Scheduled - ShareFile will be conducting a scheduled maintenance on Friday Dec 12th during the time window of 9:30 PM Eastern Time (GMT-4) to 1:00 AM Eastern Time (GMT-4). During this time users may experience minor intermittent issues with ShareFile Custom branding and Account Terms and Conditions.. We appreciate your understanding as we work to improve our services. For questions, please contact support.sharefile.com.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"【重要】EmEditor インストーラーのダウンロード導線に関するセキュリティ インシデントのお知らせ"</title><link>https://jp.emeditor.com/general/%e3%80%90%e9%87%8d%e8%a6%81%e3%80%91emeditor-%e3%82%a4%e3%83%b3%e3%82%b9%e3%83%88%e3%83%bc%e3%83%a9%e3%83%bc%e3%81%ae%e3%83%80%e3%82%a6%e3%83%b3%e3%83%ad%e3%83%bc%e3%83%89%e5%b0%8e%e7%b7%9a%e3%81%ab/</link><description>""平素より EmEditor をご利用いただき、誠にありがとうございます。 誠に遺憾ながら、EmEditor 公式サイトにおけるダウンロード導線（ホームページ上の [今すぐダウンロード] ボタン）に関し、第三者による改変が […]""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ISC's DNSSEC Look-Aside Validation Registry"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/iscs-dnssec-look-aside-validation-registry</link><description>""Decommissioned as of September 30, 2017 Introduction DLV (DNSSEC Look-aside Validation) was an extension to the DNSSECbis protocol. It was designed as a transition mechanism to assist in early DNSSEC adoption by allowing DNSSEC signing and validation of a domain whose parent was not DNSSEC-signed. DLV provided an additional entry point (besides the root zone) from which to obtain DNSSEC validation information. When it was possible to establish the DNSSEC chain of trust through the parent domain ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-14765 Out of bounds read and write in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-14765</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14765
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/12/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_18.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#december-18-2025</link><description>"Microsoft released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 143.0.3650.96) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2024-43595, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2022-33639, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2025-62223, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2025-21279, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2024-26246, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2025-60711, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2025-13223, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2025-47967, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2023-36024
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00913</link><description>""The BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix (previously know as the "BIND 9 Security Vulnerability Matrix") is a tool to help DNS operators understand the current security risk for a given version of BIND. It has two parts: The first part is a table listing all of the vulnerabilities covered by this page. The first column is a reference number for use in the tables in the second part. The second column is the CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure) number for the vulnerability, linked to its pag ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-0760
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-14174 Chromium: CVE-2025-14174 Out of bounds memory access in ANGLE"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-14174</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information. Google is aware that an exploit for CVE-2025-14174 exists in the wild.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14174
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-97 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox for iOS 144.0"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-97/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14744
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND block topmost"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/bind-block-topmost</link><description>""Name Syntax ... Blocks none Default value(s) None. Introduced Date: 1997-05-06 BIND version: 8.1.1 Deprecated Still current as of 2025-12-19 Description There is no configuration block with the name topmost. Rather this is used as a placeholder when describing the area(s) in which other statements can be used. topmost does not mean literally at the top of the configuration file. It means at the top level of the configuration hierarchy. Any statement or block that is eligible to be configu ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-4615 PAN-OS: Improper Neutralization of Input in the Management Web Interface (Severity: MEDIUM)"</title><link>https://security.paloaltonetworks.com/CVE-2025-4615</link><description>""""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-4615
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"PHP 8.4.16 Released!"</title><link>https://www.php.net/archive/2025.php#2025-12-18-4</link><description>"The PHP development team announces the immediate availability of PHP 8.4.16. This is a security release. All PHP 8.4 users are encouraged to upgrade to this version. For source downloads of PHP 8.4.16 please visit our downloads page, Windows source and binaries can also be found there. The list of changes is recorded in the ChangeLog."

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"macOS Sonoma 14.8.3"</title><link>https://support.apple.com/en-us/125888</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-43539, CVE-2025-43516, CVE-2025-43519, CVE-2025-43463, CVE-2025-43509, CVE-2025-9086, CVE-2025-43513, CVE-2025-43482, CVE-2024-7264, CVE-2025-46287, CVE-2025-46289, CVE-2025-43416, CVE-2025-43532, CVE-2025-43538, CVE-2025-46276, CVE-2025-5918, CVE-2025-43517, CVE-2025-46285, CVE-2025-43518, CVE-2025-43512, CVE-2025-43530
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Security Bulletin - December 11 2025"</title><link>https://confluence.atlassian.com/security/security-bulletin-december-11-2025-1689616574.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2023-22527, CVE-2022-35177, CVE-2024-294158, CVE-2025-271527, CVE-2025-587547, CVE-2022-420047, CVE-2024-129057, CVE-2024-216347, CVE-2023-22523, CVE-2023-46604, CVE-2022-375997, CVE-2024-130097, CVE-2025-592508, CVE-2023-22522, CVE-2016-11828, CVE-2023-497357, CVE-2025-524347, CVE-2025-6651610, CVE-2022-376037, CVE-2021-392279, CVE-2022-456937, CVE-2024-72548, CVE-2025-549888, CVE-2025-412487, CVE-2016-11818, CVE-2025-489897, CVE-2022-23521, CVE-2020-365187, CVE-2025-551638, CVE-2019-13990, CVE-2020-82037, CVE-2022-1471, CVE-2025-529998, CVE-2022-41903, CVE-2021-468777, CVE-2025-489767, CVE-2023-22518, CVE-2023-22524, CVE-2022-376019
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/12/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_10.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14372, CVE-2025-14373, CVE-2025-14174
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2025-14373 Inappropriate implementation in Toolbar"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-14373</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2021) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-14373
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>