<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:50:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"CVE-2025-11232: Invalid characters cause assert"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/cve-2025-11232</link><description>""CVE: CVE-2025-11232 Title: Invalid characters cause assert Document version: 2.0 Posting date: 29 October 2025 Program impacted: Kea Versions affected: Kea 3.0.1 -&gt; 3.0.1 3.1.1 -&gt; 3.1.2 Versions NOT affected: Kea 2.6.0 -&gt; 2.6.4 2.7.0 -&gt; 2.7.9 3.0.0 -&gt; 3.0.0 3.1.0 -&gt; 3.1.0 (Versions prior to 2.6.0 were not assessed.) Severity: High Exploitable: Remotely Description: To trigger the issue, three configuration parameters must have specific settings: "hostname-char-set" must be left at the defaul ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-11232
**CVSS Score:** 7.5</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2025-86 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 144.0.2"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2025-86/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-12380
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00913</link><description>""The BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix (previously know as the "BIND 9 Security Vulnerability Matrix") is a tool to help DNS operators understand the current security risk for a given version of BIND. It has two parts: The first part is a table listing all of the vulnerabilities covered by this page. The first column is a reference number for use in the tables in the second part. The second column is the CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure) number for the vulnerability, linked to its pag ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-0760
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SolarWinds Trust Center Security Advisories | CVE-2025-26392"</title><link>https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-26392</link><description>""10/21/2025 SolarWinds Observability Self-Hosted is susceptible to SQL injection vulnerability that may display sensitive data using a low-level account. Learn more &gt; https://www.solarwinds.com/trust-center/security-advisories/cve-2025-26392""

**CVE:** cve-2025-26392, CVE-2025-26392
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"K12201527: Overview of Quarterly Security Notifications"</title><link>https://my.f5.com/manage/s/article/K12201527?utm_source=f5support&amp;utm_medium=RSS</link><description>""Security Advisory Description F5 discloses security vulnerabilities and security exposures for F5 products in Quarterly Security Notifications (QSNs). The dates of future QSNs are published in ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-59295 Windows URL Parsing Remote Code Execution Vulnerability"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2025-59295</link><description>""Added an acknowledgement. This is an informational change only.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-59295
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-40778: Cache poisoning attacks with unsolicited RRs"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/cve-2025-40778</link><description>""CVE: CVE-2025-40778 Title: Cache poisoning attacks with unsolicited RRs Document version: 2.0 Posting date: 22 October 2025 Program impacted: BIND 9 Versions affected: BIND 9.11.0 -&gt; 9.16.50 9.18.0 -&gt; 9.18.39 9.20.0 -&gt; 9.20.13 9.21.0 -&gt; 9.21.12 BIND Supported Preview Edition 9.11.3-S1 -&gt; 9.16.50-S1 9.18.11-S1 -&gt; 9.18.39-S1 9.20.9-S1 -&gt; 9.20.13-S1 (Versions prior to 9.11.0 were not specifically assessed but are also believed to be affected) Severity: High Exploitable: Remotely Description: Un ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40778
**CVSS Score:** 8.6</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicWall SMA100 Potential Exposure of Sensitive Information in Log File"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2025-0017</link><description>""A potential exposure of sensitive information in log files in SonicWall SMA100 Series appliances may allow a remote, authenticated administrator, under certain conditions to view partial users credential data. SonicWall strongly recommends that users of the SMA 100 series products (SMA 210, 410, and 500v) upgrade to the specified fixed release version to remediate this vulnerability. SonicWall PSIRT is not aware of active exploitation of this vulnerability in the wild. No reports of a PoC have been made public and malicious use of this vulnerability has not been reported to SonicWall. CVE: CVE-2025-40603 Last updated: Oct. 30, 2025, 10:40 a.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40603
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-8677: Resource exhaustion via malformed DNSKEY handling"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/cve-2025-8677</link><description>""CVE: CVE-2025-8677 Title: Resource exhaustion via malformed DNSKEY handling Document version: 2.0 Posting date: 22 October 2025 Program impacted: BIND 9 Versions affected: BIND 9.18.0 -&gt; 9.18.39 9.20.0 -&gt; 9.20.13 9.21.0 -&gt; 9.21.12 BIND Supported Preview Edition 9.18.11-S1 -&gt; 9.18.39-S1 9.20.9-S1 -&gt; 9.20.13-S1 Severity: High Exploitable: Remotely Description: Querying for records within a specially crafted zone containing certain malformed DNSKEY records can lead to CPU exhaustion. Impact: An ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-8677
**CVSS Score:** 7.5</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"[製品]Trend Micro Mobile Security 9.8 SP5 Critical Patch 8(Build 3428) 公開のお知らせ:2025/10/28 11:00:00"</title><link>https://appweb.trendmicro.com/SupportNews/NewsDetail.aspx?id=5644</link><description>""[公開日時：2025年10月28日 (火) 11:00 ] Trend Micro Mobile Security 9.8 SP5 Critical Patch 8 (Build 3428) を下記日程にて公開いたします。 ■公開開始日 2025年10月28日 (火) ■新機能・修正内容 提供される修正、新機能については付属の Readme ファイルをご確認ください。 ■入手方法 本製品は、 最新版ダウンロードページ よりダウンロードできます。 ■製品サポート情報 ご不明な点がございましたら、弊社サポートセンターまでお問合せください。 お問合せ方法については、 こちら をご確認ください。 今後とも弊社製品をご愛顧くださいますよう、よろしくお願い申し上げます。""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/10/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_28.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-12444, CVE-2025-12433, CVE-2025-12434, CVE-2025-12441, CVE-2025-12439, CVE-2025-12443, CVE-2025-12428, CVE-2025-12446, CVE-2025-12440, CVE-2025-12447, CVE-2025-12445, CVE-2025-12432, CVE-2025-12437, CVE-2025-12438, CVE-2025-12430, CVE-2025-12436, CVE-2025-12036, CVE-2025-12431, CVE-2025-12435, CVE-2025-12429
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2025-40780: Cache poisoning due to weak PRNG"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/cve-2025-40780</link><description>""CVE: CVE-2025-40780 Title: Cache poisoning due to weak PRNG Document version: 2.0 Posting date: 22 October 2025 Program impacted: BIND 9 Versions affected: BIND 9.16.0 -&gt; 9.16.50 9.18.0 -&gt; 9.18.39 9.20.0 -&gt; 9.20.13 9.21.0 -&gt; 9.21.12 BIND Supported Preview Edition 9.16.8-S1 -&gt; 9.16.50-S1 9.18.11-S1 -&gt; 9.18.39-S1 9.20.9-S1 -&gt; 9.20.13-S1 (Versions prior to 9.11.0 were not assessed.) Severity: High Exploitable: Remotely Description: In specific circumstances, due to a weakness in the Pseudo Rand ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-40780
**CVSS Score:** 8.6</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Security Bulletin - October 21 2025"</title><link>https://confluence.atlassian.com/security/security-bulletin-october-21-2025-1652920034.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-489897, CVE-2022-23521, CVE-2023-22527, CVE-2023-22518, CVE-2023-22524, CVE-2025-221668, CVE-2025-221678, CVE-2023-22522, CVE-2023-46604, CVE-2025-79627, CVE-2023-22523, CVE-2022-41903, CVE-2025-580568, CVE-2019-13990, CVE-2025-580578, CVE-2022-1471, CVE-2025-489767
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ESET Customer Advisory: Modules Review, September 2025"</title><link>https://support-feed.eset.com/link/15370/17198922/ca8880</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2025/10/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_21.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-12036
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#october-21-2025</link><description>"Microsoft is aware of the recent Chromium security fixes. We are actively working on releasing a security fix."

**CVE:** CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2023-36024, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2024-26246, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2024-43595, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2022-33639, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2025-47967, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2025-21279
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Oracle Critical Patch Update Advisory - October 2025"</title><link>https://www.oracle.com/security-alerts/cpuoct2025.html</link><description>""""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-50074, CVE-2025-55298, CVE-2025-5889, CVE-2025-9086, CVE-2025-5987, CVE-2024-50609, CVE-2025-62588, CVE-2025-53043, CVE-2023-34053, CVE-2025-1735, CVE-2025-23166, CVE-2024-57699, CVE-2025-30474, CVE-2025-53071, CVE-2025-61758, CVE-2025-61760, CVE-2025-61751, CVE-2020-15250, CVE-2024-54160, CVE-2025-62591, CVE-2025-30754, CVE-2025-32988, CVE-2025-27113, CVE-2025-62290, CVE-2024-7254, CVE-2025-61749, CVE-2025-5351, CVE-2024-52533, CVE-2025-53041, CVE-2025-48924, CVE-2025-4330, CVE-2025-5449, CVE-2025-50075, CVE-2025-7339, CVE-2025-61753, CVE-2025-53072, CVE-2025-27533, CVE-2025-32414, CVE-2025-53060, CVE-2025-31651, CVE-2025-62476, CVE-2024-12254, CVE-2025-53066, CVE-2025-48988, CVE-2025-53034, CVE-2025-61763, CVE-2024-28168, CVE-2025-4435, CVE-2025-7425, CVE-2025-32990, CVE-2024-37371, CVE-2025-9232, CVE-2025-53061, CVE-2025-4802, CVE-2025-62590, CVE-2025-53036, CVE-2025-1795, CVE-2025-50063, CVE-2025-43228, CVE-2025-8885, CVE-2025-59475, CVE-2025-53047, CVE-2025-53063, CVE-2025-30752, CVE-2025-27363, CVE-2025-27818, CVE-2023-26551, CVE-2025-3576, CVE-2023-2976, CVE-2025-43227, CVE-2025-25724, CVE-2025-62478, CVE-2024-12718, CVE-2025-53053, CVE-2024-8088, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2025-61757, CVE-2024-35195, CVE-2023-45853, CVE-2022-22968, CVE-2025-62589, CVE-2025-43240, CVE-2025-59476, CVE-2024-41909, CVE-2025-53062, CVE-2025-53070, CVE-2024-38820, CVE-2025-53044, CVE-2025-55163, CVE-2024-4140, CVE-2025-49796, CVE-2025-62289, CVE-2025-53065, CVE-2025-53051, CVE-2025-53035, CVE-2025-23184, CVE-2025-53054, CVE-2024-9287, CVE-2025-61764, CVE-2025-48795, CVE-2025-53506, CVE-2025-61761, CVE-2025-62587, CVE-2025-61752, CVE-2021-28165, CVE-2025-53052, CVE-2020-17521, CVE-2025-31257, CVE-2025-24970, CVE-2020-13956, CVE-2025-3573, CVE-2025-62481, CVE-2025-31650, CVE-2025-6395, CVE-2025-50181, CVE-2025-62480, CVE-2023-44483, CVE-2025-1220, CVE-2024-13009, CVE-2025-47273, CVE-2025-9230, CVE-2025-53037, CVE-2023-34055, CVE-2025-31278, CVE-2025-41249, CVE-2025-61882, CVE-2022-25647, CVE-2025-49128, CVE-2024-48014, CVE-2025-5878, CVE-2025-53068, CVE-2025-61754, CVE-2024-52046, CVE-2024-28182, CVE-2022-0839, CVE-2025-53864, CVE-2025-54090, CVE-2023-26553, CVE-2025-24189, CVE-2025-61750, CVE-2025-61755, CVE-2025-55212, CVE-2025-7962, CVE-2025-50182, CVE-2025-27587, CVE-2024-38819, CVE-2025-4138, CVE-2025-27817, CVE-2023-26555, CVE-2025-43265, CVE-2024-23807, CVE-2025-53050, CVE-2024-56406, CVE-2024-38827, CVE-2022-24329, CVE-2025-53547, CVE-2025-62287, CVE-2025-53059, CVE-2025-22235, CVE-2023-1370, CVE-2021-3712, CVE-2025-50065, CVE-2025-62288, CVE-2025-22227, CVE-2025-53048, CVE-2025-61884, CVE-2025-61756, CVE-2025-53069, CVE-2025-50059, CVE-2025-32415, CVE-2024-50608, CVE-2025-4575, CVE-2023-33201, CVE-2025-53046, CVE-2025-0411, CVE-2025-30761, CVE-2025-6021, CVE-2025-53056, CVE-2025-24855, CVE-2025-31273, CVE-2025-62475, CVE-2023-7256, CVE-2025-59474, CVE-2025-49124, CVE-2025-10148, CVE-2025-8058, CVE-2025-5399, CVE-2024-12133, CVE-2025-53816, CVE-2024-38821, CVE-2025-53042, CVE-2024-51504, CVE-2025-61762, CVE-2021-22897, CVE-2025-43211, CVE-2025-4878, CVE-2025-52520, CVE-2024-52577, CVE-2025-6965, CVE-2025-49794, CVE-2025-53067, CVE-2024-12797, CVE-2025-1948, CVE-2025-53045, CVE-2024-8006, CVE-2023-26554, CVE-2025-62641, CVE-2025-27210, CVE-2025-4517, CVE-2024-35164, CVE-2025-5372, CVE-2025-8916, CVE-2025-53064, CVE-2024-12798, CVE-2025-61885, CVE-2025-23084, CVE-2025-53049, CVE-2025-48734, CVE-2025-59375, CVE-2025-22228, CVE-2025-48976, CVE-2025-62592, CVE-2024-9143, CVE-2023-5072, CVE-2025-61748, CVE-2024-6923, CVE-2025-53055, CVE-2025-50106, CVE-2025-49125, CVE-2021-3711, CVE-2025-53058, CVE-2025-6491, CVE-2025-53057, CVE-2025-57803, CVE-2023-26552, CVE-2025-43216, CVE-2025-27553, CVE-2025-61881, CVE-2025-52434, CVE-2025-62479, CVE-2025-52999, CVE-2025-31672, CVE-2025-22233, CVE-2025-5115, CVE-2025-4373, CVE-2025-48989, CVE-2025-32728, CVE-2020-11988, CVE-2025-53040, CVE-2025-26333, CVE-2025-61759, CVE-2025-53643, CVE-2024-47554, CVE-2025-4877, CVE-2025-62477, CVE-2025-32989, CVE-2025-25193, CVE-2024-37370, CVE-2025-43212, CVE-2025-5318, CVE-2024-26462, CVE-2025-27209, CVE-2025-58057, CVE-2024-38828, CVE-2025-49795, CVE-2025-4949, CVE-2025-30749
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Potential Security Impact of ASP.NET Vulnerability on NetBak PC Agent"</title><link>https://www.qnap.com/en-us/security-advisory/QSA-25-44</link><description>""Summary Microsoft has disclosed a security vulnerability (CVE-2025-55315) affecting ASP.NET Core that could allow an attacker to b ... More""

**CVE:** CVE-2025-55315
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with their ShareFile account"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/1qlr4l391y3t</link><description>""Oct 20 , 17:31 EDT Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Oct 20 , 17:31 EDT Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Oct 20 , 17:25 EDT Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Oct 20 , 17:22 EDT Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Oct 20 , 17:06 EDT Update - We are continuing to monitor for any further issues. Oct 20 , 17:03 EDT Monitoring - ShareFile is now operational, and we are continuing to monitor its performance closely. Oct 20 , 15:43 EDT Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented. Oct 20 , 15:18 EDT Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Oct 20 , 15:00 EDT Identified - The issue has been identified and a fix is being implemented. Oct 20 , 14:47 EDT Update - We are continuing to investigate this issue. Oct 20 , 14:42 EDT Update - We are currently experiencing an outage affecting ShareFile due to multiple service disruptions on our cloud provider's side. Our team is actively monitoring the situation and awaiting further updates from the provider. Oct 20 , 14:29 EDT Investigating - Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing issues with their accounts. We are investigating this issue and we will provide updates here as soon as available.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Some ShareFile customers may be experiencing latency in the application"</title><link>https://status.sharefile.com/incidents/w5cf8cjvxtvd</link><description>""Oct 20 , 06:13 EDT Resolved - This incident has been resolved. Oct 20 , 06:13 EDT Investigating - We are currently investigating this issue. Oct 20 , 05:47 EDT Monitoring - A fix has been implemented and we are monitoring the results. Oct 20 , 05:27 EDT Update - ShareFile is now operational, and we are continuing to monitor its performance closely. Oct 20 , 05:03 EDT Update - We are currently experiencing an outage affecting ShareFile due to multiple service disruptions on our cloud provider’s side. Our team is actively monitoring the situation and awaiting further updates from the provider. Oct 20 , 04:00 EDT Investigating - We are investigating customer reports of an issue impacting performance of ShareFile causing slowness in the application and increased error rates. We will provide updates here as soon as possible.""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>