<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>脆弱性情報の更新確認RSS</title><link>https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml</link><description>特定の脆弱性情報の更新情報</description><atom:link href="https://AgetakoSec.github.io/vulnerability-update-rss/rss.xml" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:53:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2441 Use after free in CSS"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2441</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information. Google is aware that an exploit for CVE-2026-2441 exists in the wild.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2441
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2026-0229 PAN-OS: Denial of Service in Advanced DNS Security Feature (Severity: MEDIUM)"</title><link>https://security.paloaltonetworks.com/CVE-2026-0229</link><description>""""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-0229
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2323 Inappropriate implementation in Downloads"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2323</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2323
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2316 Insufficient policy enforcement in Frames"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2316</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2316
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2650 Heap buffer overflow in Media"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2650</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2650
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04967 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processor BIOS, INTEL-SA-01234, 2025.3 IPU, UEFI Reference Firmware Advisory., Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04967en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04967 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processor BIOS, INTEL-SA-01234, 2025.3 IPU, UEFI Reference Firmware Advisory., Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04999 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant AMD DL/XL Servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors, AMD-SB-3023:AMD Server Vulnerabilities, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04999en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04999 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant AMD DL/XL Servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors, AMD-SB-3023:AMD Server Vulnerabilities, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#february-14-2026</link><description>"Microsoft released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 145.0.3800.58) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. The Chromium team reported that CVE-2026-2441 has an exploit in the wild, and this update contains a fix for it. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** "CVE-2026-0102"
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2319 Race in DevTools"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2319</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2319
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Supported Platforms"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/supported-platforms</link><description>""BIND 9 Operating System Support When a new branch of BIND 9 is released, ISC normally tests it to ensure compatibility with the current versions of major operating systems (OSes) at that time. In general, that branch of BIND 9 will support those major operating systems until either that version of BIND 9 or that version of the OS reaches end-of-life (EOL) status. The table below lists the operating systems supported by the current versions of BIND 9. Legend: 💚 Supported 🔵 Best effort 🟧 Commun ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04864 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpiVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01244, 2025.2 IPU, Intel Processor Advisory, Local Denial of Service Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04864en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04864 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpiVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01244, 2025.2 IPU, Intel Processor Advisory, Local Denial of Service Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2320 Inappropriate implementation in File input"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2320</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2320
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2313 Use after free in CSS"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2313</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2313
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-10 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 147.0.4, ESR 140.7.1, and ESR 115.32.1"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-10/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2447
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04939 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01312, Intel TDX Module Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04939en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04939 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01312, Intel TDX Module Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2026/02/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_23.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-3062, CVE-2026-3061, CVE-2026-3063
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Security Bulletin - February 17 2026"</title><link>https://confluence.atlassian.com/security/security-bulletin-february-17-2026-1722256046.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2023-22524, CVE-2025-593438, CVE-2025-665169, CVE-2022-1471, CVE-2023-22527, CVE-2023-22518, CVE-2022-259277, CVE-2025-660218, CVE-2019-201497, CVE-2025-666758, CVE-2025-489767, CVE-2022-41903, CVE-2022-258837, CVE-2025-92879, CVE-2022-23521, CVE-2023-22522, CVE-2025-487348, CVE-2024-576997, CVE-2020-284697, CVE-2019-13990, CVE-2025-412497, CVE-2023-22523, CVE-2025-92889, CVE-2023-46604
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-17 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 140.8"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-17/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2759, CVE-2026-2771, CVE-2026-2783, CVE-2026-2789, CVE-2026-2772, CVE-2026-2767, CVE-2026-2764, CVE-2026-2758, CVE-2026-2762, CVE-2026-2779, CVE-2026-2788, CVE-2026-2768, CVE-2026-2766, CVE-2026-2773, CVE-2026-2777, CVE-2026-2781, CVE-2026-2782, CVE-2026-2780, CVE-2026-2793, CVE-2026-2791, CVE-2026-2761, CVE-2026-2757, CVE-2026-2765, CVE-2026-2770, CVE-2026-2792, CVE-2026-2785, CVE-2026-2774, CVE-2026-2787, CVE-2026-2776, CVE-2026-2784, CVE-2026-2790, CVE-2026-2769, CVE-2026-2763, CVE-2026-2760, CVE-2026-2786, CVE-2026-2775, CVE-2026-2778
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-16 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 148"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-16/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2759, CVE-2026-2805, CVE-2026-2771, CVE-2026-2783, CVE-2026-2789, CVE-2026-2772, CVE-2026-2767, CVE-2026-2800, CVE-2026-2764, CVE-2026-2758, CVE-2026-2762, CVE-2026-2806, CVE-2026-2779, CVE-2026-2788, CVE-2026-2804, CVE-2026-2768, CVE-2026-2766, CVE-2026-2773, CVE-2026-2777, CVE-2026-2781, CVE-2026-2782, CVE-2026-2803, CVE-2026-2796, CVE-2026-2780, CVE-2026-2791, CVE-2026-2793, CVE-2026-2761, CVE-2026-2757, CVE-2026-2801, CVE-2026-2765, CVE-2026-2770, CVE-2026-2792, CVE-2026-2785, CVE-2026-2774, CVE-2026-2787, CVE-2026-2795, CVE-2026-2776, CVE-2026-2784, CVE-2026-2790, CVE-2026-2802, CVE-2026-2769, CVE-2026-2763, CVE-2026-2799, CVE-2026-2760, CVE-2026-2786, CVE-2026-2798, CVE-2026-2775, CVE-2026-2807, CVE-2026-2797, CVE-2026-2778
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2648 Heap buffer overflow in PDFium"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2648</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2648
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"ISC's Software Support Policy and Version Numbering"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00896</link><description>""The purpose of this article is to help users determine how long a given ISC release is likely to be supported. This information is useful when deciding when to schedule a migration, or in some cases, to help determine which version to migrate to when updating. This is a rough guide, not a guarantee, and release dates are approximate. For the most current information on the status of any particular software version, please refer to the software status listed on the downloads page. BIND 9 (updated ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2026/02/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_18.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2650, CVE-2026-2649, CVE-2026-2648
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF05008 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD, Synergy, Edgeline, MicroServer, and Alletra Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01396, 2026.1 IPU, Intel Processor Firmware Advisory, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf05008en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF05008 rev.2 - Certain HPE ProLiant DL/ML/XD, Synergy, Edgeline, MicroServer, and Alletra Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01396, 2026.1 IPU, Intel Processor Firmware Advisory, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF05021 rev.1 - Certain HPE ProLiant AMD DL/XL Servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors, AMD-SB-7059: Guest Initiated Machine Check Errors, Denial of Service Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf05021en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF05021 rev.1 - Certain HPE ProLiant AMD DL/XL Servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors, AMD-SB-7059: Guest Initiated Machine Check Errors, Denial of Service Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04937 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04937en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04937 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01280, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Chipset Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-13 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox 148"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-13/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2759, CVE-2026-2805, CVE-2026-2771, CVE-2026-2783, CVE-2026-2789, CVE-2026-2772, CVE-2026-2767, CVE-2026-2794, CVE-2026-2800, CVE-2026-2764, CVE-2026-2758, CVE-2026-2762, CVE-2026-2806, CVE-2026-2779, CVE-2026-2788, CVE-2026-2804, CVE-2026-2768, CVE-2026-2766, CVE-2026-2773, CVE-2026-2777, CVE-2026-2781, CVE-2026-2782, CVE-2026-2803, CVE-2026-2796, CVE-2026-2780, CVE-2026-2791, CVE-2026-2793, CVE-2026-2761, CVE-2026-2757, CVE-2026-2801, CVE-2026-2765, CVE-2026-2770, CVE-2026-2792, CVE-2026-2785, CVE-2026-2774, CVE-2026-2787, CVE-2026-2795, CVE-2026-2776, CVE-2026-2784, CVE-2026-2790, CVE-2026-2802, CVE-2026-2769, CVE-2026-2763, CVE-2026-2799, CVE-2026-2760, CVE-2026-2786, CVE-2026-2798, CVE-2026-2775, CVE-2026-2807, CVE-2026-2797, CVE-2026-2778
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#february-20-2026</link><description>"Microsoft released the latest Microsoft Edge Stable Channel (Version 145.0.3800.70) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2023-36024, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2025-60711, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2025-62223, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2025-47967, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2022-33639, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2026-0102, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2024-26246, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2025-21279, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2026-21223, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2026-2441, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2025-13223, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2024-43595
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2322 Heap buffer overflow in Codecs"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2322</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2322
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2026/02/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_13.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2441
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND statement forwarders"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/bind-statement-forwarders</link><description>""Name forwarders Syntax forwarders { ; [;...] }; Blocks options Default value(s) There are no default acls defined Introduced Date: 1997-05-06 BIND version: 8.1.1 Deprecated Still current as of 2025-11-24 Description The forwarders statement allows users to define lists of addresses. Each list is named and can be referenced by this name in many other configuration elements where one of more addresses are needed as arguments. If the same set ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2314 Heap buffer overflow in Codecs"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2314</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2314
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"CVE-2026-2318"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2318</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2318
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2317 Inappropriate implementation in Animation"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2317</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2317
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04938 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01313, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Xeon Processor Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04938en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04938 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01313, 2025.3 IPU, Intel Xeon Processor Firmware Advisory, Multiple Vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-15 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox ESR 140.8"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-15/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2759, CVE-2026-2771, CVE-2026-2783, CVE-2026-2789, CVE-2026-2772, CVE-2026-2767, CVE-2026-2764, CVE-2026-2758, CVE-2026-2762, CVE-2026-2779, CVE-2026-2788, CVE-2026-2768, CVE-2026-2766, CVE-2026-2773, CVE-2026-2777, CVE-2026-2781, CVE-2026-2782, CVE-2026-2780, CVE-2026-2793, CVE-2026-2791, CVE-2026-2761, CVE-2026-2757, CVE-2026-2765, CVE-2026-2770, CVE-2026-2792, CVE-2026-2785, CVE-2026-2774, CVE-2026-2787, CVE-2026-2776, CVE-2026-2784, CVE-2026-2790, CVE-2026-2769, CVE-2026-2763, CVE-2026-2760, CVE-2026-2786, CVE-2026-2775, CVE-2026-2778
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW05011 rev.1 - Telco Service Activator, Improper Input Validation"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw05011en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW05011 rev.1 - Telco Service Activator, Improper Input Validation""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-11 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Thunderbird 147.0.2 and 140.7.2"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-11/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2447
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-14 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox ESR 115.33"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-14/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2759, CVE-2026-2771, CVE-2026-2789, CVE-2026-2772, CVE-2026-2764, CVE-2026-2758, CVE-2026-2788, CVE-2026-2777, CVE-2026-2773, CVE-2026-2793, CVE-2026-2761, CVE-2026-2757, CVE-2026-2770, CVE-2026-2774, CVE-2026-2787, CVE-2026-2776, CVE-2026-2769, CVE-2026-2763, CVE-2026-2760, CVE-2026-2775, CVE-2026-2778
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF05023 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors, AMD-SB-7059: Guest Initiated Machine Check Errors, Denial of Service Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf05023en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF05023 rev.1 - Certain HPE SimpliVity Servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors, AMD-SB-7059: Guest Initiated Machine Check Errors, Denial of Service Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Chromium: CVE-2026-2649 Integer overflow in V8"</title><link>https://msrc.microsoft.com/update-guide/vulnerability/CVE-2026-2649</link><description>""This CVE was assigned by Chrome. Microsoft Edge (Chromium-based) ingests Chromium, which addresses this vulnerability. Please see [Google Chrome Releases](https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2024 ) for more information.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2649
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"MFSA 2026-12 Security Vulnerabilities fixed in Firefox for iOS 147.4"</title><link>https://www.mozilla.org/en-US/security/advisories/mfsa2026-12/</link><description>""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2634
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/aa-00913</link><description>""The BIND 9 Software Vulnerability Matrix (previously know as the "BIND 9 Security Vulnerability Matrix") is a tool to help DNS operators understand the current security risk for a given version of BIND. It has two parts: The first part is a table listing all of the vulnerabilities covered by this page. The first column is a reference number for use in the tables in the second part. The second column is the CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposure) number for the vulnerability, linked to its pag ...""

**CVE:** CVE-2024-0760
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW05012 rev.1 - Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM) OnGuard Software for Linux"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw05012en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW05012 rev.1 - Local Privilege Escalation Vulnerability in HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager (CPPM) OnGuard Software for Linux""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stork Quickstart guide"</title><link>https://kb.isc.org/docs/stork-quickstart-guide</link><description>""Introduction Installing Stork can seem somewhat confusing at first. The purpose of this quickstart guide is to layout the installation process in steps grouped by package manager or OS. Choose your OS/package manager from the table of contents on the right hand side to jump directly to the section that will cover the installation on your system. Stork Agent Since the Stork Agent may need to be installed more than once on disparate systems (example: to monitor BIND and Kea installations which ...""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04983 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Orchestrator software, Prototype Pollution Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04983en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04983 rev.1 - HPE Telco Service Orchestrator software, Prototype Pollution Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF05016 rev.2 - Certain HPE StoreEasy Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01396, 2026.1 IPU, Intel Processor Firmware Advisory, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf05016en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF05016 rev.2 - Certain HPE StoreEasy Servers Using Certain Intel Processors, INTEL-SA-01396, 2026.1 IPU, Intel Processor Firmware Advisory, Local Escalation of Privilege Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#february-17-2026</link><description>"Microsoft released the latest Microsoft Edge Extended Stable Channel (Version 144.0.3719.130) which incorporates the latest Security Updates of the Chromium project. The Chromium team reported that CVE-2026-2441 has an exploit in the wild, and this update contains a fix for it. For more information, see the Security Update Guide."

**CVE:** CVE-2026-2441
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF04963 rev.2 - Certain HPE SimpliVity servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors. AMD-SB-3029: Stale Translation Lookaside Buffer (TLB) Entry Vulnerability, Local Unauthorized Access Vulnerability"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf04963en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF04963 rev.2 - Certain HPE SimpliVity servers Using Certain AMD EPYC Processors. AMD-SB-3029: Stale Translation Lookaside Buffer (TLB) Entry Vulnerability, Local Unauthorized Access Vulnerability""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Microsoft Edge Security Updates"</title><link>https://learn.microsoft.com/en-us/deployedge/microsoft-edge-relnotes-security#february-23-2026</link><description>"Microsoft is aware of the recent Chromium security fixes. We are actively working on releasing a security fix."

**CVE:** CVE-2024-38219, CVE-2024-43489, CVE-2023-36888, CVE-2023-21794, CVE-2022-21930, CVE-2021-37976, CVE-2023-0941, CVE-2023-23374, CVE-2023-36878, CVE-2023-33143, CVE-2025-21185, CVE-2021-21166, CVE-2023-36024, CVE-2022-44688, CVE-2022-29146, CVE-2022-24523, CVE-2024-26247, CVE-2023-28286, CVE-2024-38218, CVE-2024-49054, CVE-2022-26908, CVE-2023-2136, CVE-2022-21931, CVE-2024-38209, CVE-2024-20709, CVE-2024-29981, CVE-2022-44708, CVE-2022-23261, CVE-2021-30633, CVE-2025-21253, CVE-2025-60711, CVE-2023-38173, CVE-2022-26912, CVE-2021-38669, CVE-2025-49713, CVE-2024-49023, CVE-2024-43596, CVE-2021-38000, CVE-2021-26439, CVE-2025-6558, CVE-2024-21326, CVE-2023-36562, CVE-2023-7024, CVE-2023-36034, CVE-2022-35796, CVE-2024-4761, CVE-2025-21342, CVE-2024-21388, CVE-2023-36022, CVE-2025-62223, CVE-2025-5419, CVE-2024-26196, CVE-2023-2033, CVE-2024-29049, CVE-2024-21423, CVE-2022-30127, CVE-2023-3079, CVE-2024-38207, CVE-2022-33636, CVE-2023-29345, CVE-2020-15999, CVE-2021-24113, CVE-2024-5274, CVE-2025-21401, CVE-2021-31937, CVE-2022-26909, CVE-2024-43580, CVE-2024-20721, CVE-2022-30128, CVE-2024-38156, CVE-2024-21337, CVE-2025-29825, CVE-2025-29795, CVE-2024-2883, CVE-2021-36931, CVE-2024-30055, CVE-2025-47967, CVE-2025-29796, CVE-2022-23264, CVE-2023-36787, CVE-2022-0609, CVE-2022-23258, CVE-2024-7965, CVE-2024-26192, CVE-2020-16009, CVE-2023-36727, CVE-2023-36880, CVE-2024-49041, CVE-2024-26188, CVE-2022-3075, CVE-2022-33639, CVE-2025-47181, CVE-2023-38157, CVE-2025-29834, CVE-2023-28301, CVE-2022-26905, CVE-2022-24475, CVE-2025-47182, CVE-2024-38083, CVE-2025-21267, CVE-2021-30632, CVE-2026-0102, CVE-2021-36928, CVE-2024-43566, CVE-2023-28261, CVE-2023-36027, CVE-2022-21954, CVE-2021-43220, CVE-2023-21719, CVE-2024-26246, CVE-2022-21970, CVE-2024-43579, CVE-2024-29987, CVE-2021-42308, CVE-2024-21385, CVE-2023-35618, CVE-2022-26891, CVE-2022-29144, CVE-2023-35392, CVE-2022-26895, CVE-2024-38103, CVE-2021-36930, CVE-2024-21382, CVE-2025-10585, CVE-2024-30056, CVE-2023-38174, CVE-2023-21795, CVE-2022-4135, CVE-2025-6554, CVE-2022-41115, CVE-2021-30551, CVE-2024-41879, CVE-2025-21283, CVE-2025-47964, CVE-2024-43577, CVE-2022-21929, CVE-2024-4671, CVE-2023-4863, CVE-2020-1195, CVE-2024-43472, CVE-2024-21399, CVE-2025-21262, CVE-2023-38187, CVE-2025-26643, CVE-2024-20675, CVE-2024-43587, CVE-2022-23263, CVE-2021-33741, CVE-2023-21775, CVE-2024-26167, CVE-2023-38158, CVE-2023-29354, CVE-2023-36029, CVE-2021-31982, CVE-2021-21148, CVE-2020-1341, CVE-2023-5217, CVE-2024-38210, CVE-2023-36883, CVE-2024-49025, CVE-2024-0519, CVE-2021-4102, CVE-2024-29057, CVE-2020-6418, CVE-2021-30554, CVE-2024-21383, CVE-2022-23262, CVE-2024-21387, CVE-2021-37973, CVE-2023-33145, CVE-2024-43578, CVE-2022-2294, CVE-2020-16017, CVE-2021-43221, CVE-2024-30057, CVE-2023-6345, CVE-2022-38012, CVE-2022-41035, CVE-2022-22021, CVE-2023-36559, CVE-2023-21796, CVE-2021-34475, CVE-2024-29986, CVE-2020-16013, CVE-2021-38641, CVE-2021-21206, CVE-2024-4947, CVE-2024-26163, CVE-2024-38222, CVE-2023-28284, CVE-2025-21279, CVE-2024-30058, CVE-2022-26894, CVE-2026-21223, CVE-2022-26899, CVE-2023-36014, CVE-2023-21720, CVE-2026-2441, CVE-2024-38208, CVE-2023-36026, CVE-2022-33649, CVE-2025-21408, CVE-2022-1364, CVE-2025-25000, CVE-2025-24201, CVE-2024-21336, CVE-2022-29147, CVE-2022-30192, CVE-2021-37975, CVE-2021-30563, CVE-2024-39379, CVE-2023-29350, CVE-2025-4664, CVE-2023-24935, CVE-2023-36741, CVE-2024-38221, CVE-2023-44323, CVE-2021-36929, CVE-2025-13223, CVE-2022-33680, CVE-2023-36735, CVE-2024-38093, CVE-2024-29991, CVE-2021-38003, CVE-2021-38642, CVE-2021-34506, CVE-2022-3723, CVE-2025-53791, CVE-2023-29334, CVE-2025-21404, CVE-2025-21399, CVE-2021-21220, CVE-2024-7971, CVE-2024-38082, CVE-2023-36008, CVE-2022-33638, CVE-2025-47963, CVE-2021-21224, CVE-2022-2856, CVE-2021-21193, CVE-2022-26900, CVE-2024-43496, CVE-2022-1096, CVE-2023-36887, CVE-2022-4262, CVE-2021-26436, CVE-2025-2783, CVE-2024-43595
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SQL injection in forward module"</title><link>https://fortiguard.fortinet.com/psirt/#5575</link><description>""""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBHF05004 rev.1 - Certain HPE ProLiant Servers Using Certain Intel Processor BIOS, INTEL-SA-01406, Intel Quick Assist Technology (Intel QAT) Advisory, Multiple vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbhf05004en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBHF05004 rev.1 - Certain HPE ProLiant Servers Using Certain Intel Processor BIOS, INTEL-SA-01406, Intel Quick Assist Technology (Intel QAT) Advisory, Multiple vulnerabilities""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"Stable Channel Update for Desktop"</title><link>https://chromereleases.googleblog.com/2026/02/stable-channel-update-for-desktop_12.html</link><description>""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"HPESBNW04998 rev.1 - Prototype Pollution Vulnerability in HPE Telco Network Function Virtualization Orchestrator"</title><link>https://support.hpe.com/hpesc/public/docDisplay?docId=hpesbnw04998en_us&amp;docLocale=en_US</link><description>""HPESBNW04998 rev.1 - Prototype Pollution Vulnerability in HPE Telco Network Function Virtualization Orchestrator""

**CVE:** 
**CVSS Score:** </description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>"SonicOS multiple post-authentication vulnerabilities"</title><link>https://psirt.global.sonicwall.com/vuln-detail/SNWLID-2026-0001</link><description>""1) CVE-2026-0399 - Multiple SonicOS post-authentication Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerabilities Multiple post-authentication Stack-based Buffer Overflow vulnerabilities in SonicOS allows a remote attacker to crash a firewall. CVSS Score: 4.9 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H CWE-121: Stack-based Buffer Overflow 2) CVE-2026-0400 - SonicOS post-authentication Format String vulnerability A post-authentication Format String vulnerability in SonicOS allows a remote attacker to crash a firewall. CVSS Score: 4.9 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H CWE-134: Use of Externally-Controlled Format String 3) CVE-2026-0401 - SonicOS post-authentication NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability A post-authentication NULL Pointer Dereference vulnerability in SonicOS allows a remote attacker to crash a firewall. CVSS Score: 4.9 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H CWE-476: NULL Pointer Dereference 4) CVE-2026-0402 - SonicOS post-authentication Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability A post-authentication Out-of-bounds Read vulnerability in SonicOS allows a remote attacker to crash a firewall. CVSS Score: 4.9 CVSS Vector: CVSS:3.1/AV:N/AC:L/PR:H/UI:N/S:U/C:N/I:N/A:H CWE-125: Out-of-bounds Read CVE: CVE-2026-0399, CVE-2026-0400, CVE-2026-0401, CVE-2026-0402 Last updated: Feb. 24, 2026, 11:46 a.m.""

**CVE:** CVE-2026-0402, CVE-2026-0401, CVE-2026-0399, CVE-2026-0400
**CVSS Score:** 3</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>